<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<journals_list>
   <journal>
      <title>Advanced Journal of Graduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://journals.aijr.in/index.php/ajgr</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>Advanced Journal of Graduate Research (ISSN:2456-7108) is a refereed journal dedicated to publishing research work carried out by Bachelor/Master Degree students under the supervision of a faculty member. Normally research work carried out as a part of the undergraduate course or graduate course in the form of final year thesis (course project) will be considered in this specific graduate journal. Any mentored student may submit articles related to all area of Science and Technology including Life Science, Computer Science, Mathematics, Environmental Science, Earth Science, Agriculture Science, Medical Science, Chemical Science, Physical Science. This journal accepts original research article, review article and survey article. Normal publication is free in this journal with open access availability of published article.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>American Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://www.ajuronline.org/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>American Journal of Undergraduate Research (AJUR) is a national, independent, peer reviewed, open-source, no-cost-to-authors, quarterly, multidisciplinary student research journal. AJUR is indexed. AJUR (print ISSN 1536-4585, web ISSN 2375-8732) was established in 2002.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>ANTHROJOURNAL: The Collegiate Journal of Anthropology</title>
      <URL>http://anthrojournal.com/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>AnthroJournal is an open-source journal of outstanding scholarly research papers and reports authored primarily by undergraduate and graduate college students. The content represents the results of extensive research undertaken by students during the course of their education and designed to advance scholarship in anthropology and related fields.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>EVOS Journal</title>
      <URL>http://evostudies.org/evos-journal/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>EvoS Journal: The Journal of the Evolutionary Studies Consortium is a journal designed to promote the education of evolutionary theory in colleges and universities. EvoS Journal welcomes work from all academic disciplines as well as interdisciplinary scholarship that incorporates evolutionary theory across areas of study.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Furman University Electronic Journal of Undergraduate Mathematics</title>
      <URL>http://math.furman.edu/~mwoodard/fuejum/welcome.html</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description/>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Inquiries Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.inquiriesjournal.com/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>Inquiries Journal is an open-access, multidisciplinary student journal focused on presenting student scholarship in the social sciences, arts, and humanities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>International Collegiate Science Journal</title>
      <URL>http://icsjournal.org/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The International Collegiate Science Journal is a revolutionary publication with a mission to translate science from obscure to captivating. We want to write exciting articles explaining why our brain forgets names of people we just met, why it rains diamonds on Saturn, how you can travel to the Caribbean in a second through virtual reality, how we may be able to live for 200 years in the near future, and other interesting topics that you will want to read. Through an online and print magazine, we hope to create an environment where anyone can uncover science and discover all that it can do. This is not just a journal. This is ICSJ.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>International Journal of Exercise Science</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.wku.edu/ijes/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The primary aim of the International Journal of Exercise Science is to engage undergraduate and graduate students in scholarly activity as authors and reviewers as they develop into professionals. In addition to providing students with an outlet for manuscript submission, the Journal will engage students as peer reviewers, thus providing students with a more encompassing experience with regards to scholarly activity. All student authors who have a manuscript accepted in the Journal will be added to the reviewer pool and may have the opportunity to serve as a peer reviewer on future submissions.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Involve - A Journal of Mathematics</title>
      <URL>http://msp.berkeley.edu/involve/about/cover/cover.html</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>Involve showcases and encourages high-quality mathematical research involving students from all academic levels and universities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal for Undergraduate Ethnography</title>
      <URL>http://undergraduateethnography.org/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The JUE is an online publication for undergraduate academic writing. The JUE seeks to distribute original scholarly ethnographies from a variety of disciplinary areas.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Integrated Social Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://www.jiss.org/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The Journal of Integrated Social Sciences is a web-based, peer-reviewed journal committed to the scholarly investigation of social phenomena. We especially encourage students and their faculty advisors to submit the results of their investigations.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Student Research</title>
      <URL>http://www.jofsr.com/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The Journal of Student Research is an electronic, academic, multidisciplinary, peer-reviewed journal devoted to the rapid dissemination of current research.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Ethnic Minority Psychology</title>
      <URL>http://www.juempsychology.com/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The Journal of Undergraduate Ethnic Minority Psychology (JUEMP) is an edited and refereed on-line journal devoted to publishing empirical research (extended abstracts as well as quantitative and qualitative full-length manuscripts) authored by university undergraduate students. We invite empirical research submissions that are from ethnic minority’s unique perspectives or that focus on the thoughts and behaviors of ethnic minority populations.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Research in Physics</title>
      <URL>http://www.jurp.org/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>JURP is a peer-reviewed online journal of the Society of Physics Students (SPS) and Sigma Pi Sigma, the physics honor society.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Young Investigators</title>
      <URL>http://www.jyi.org/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The Journal of Young Investigators is the largest and most prestigious journal of undergraduate research. We accept submissions from all over the world and in all scientific disciplines (including biology, chemistry, physics, engineering, mathematics, and social sciences). Our journal was founded more than 20 years ago and received a generous endowment from Burroughs Welcome Fund to help finance our mission of enhancing publication opportunities for undergraduate researchers. We are entirely run by undergraduates living in more than a dozen countries. To learn about submitting to the journal our joining our staff, please see our website at jyi.org.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Learning &amp; Teaching: The International Journal of Higher Education in the Social Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://journals.berghahnbooks.com/ltss/index.php?pg=home</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>Learning and Teaching (LATISS) is a peer-reviewed journal that uses the social sciences to reflect critically on learning and teaching in the changing context of higher education. The journal invites students and staff to explore their education practices in the light of changes in their institutions, national higher education policies, the strategies of international agencies and developments associated with the so-called international knowledge economy.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Online Journal for Undergraduate Research in the Marine and Aquatic Sciences</title>
      <URL>https://sites.google.com/site/marscijournal/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>MarSci is an inter-institutional venue for publishing undergraduate research manuscripts pertaining to the marine and aquatic sciences. Students interested in writing a manuscript based on their undergraduate research experience, as well as research advisors to undergraduates, should find MarSci to be the perfect opportunity for undergraduates to engage in the process of submission and publication, a unique learning experience that is not typically available to most undergraduate scientists.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>openamericas.org</title>
      <URL>https://openamericas.org/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>Open Americas (OA) is a platform for sharing content that engages with contemporary social issues issues facing the Western Hemisphere. We advocate a diversity of thought through information, whether research, literature, reviews, or photographs. OA does not strictly adhere to any political or religious doctrine and encourages open, respectful debate and critical thought. We were founded by a group of female undergraduate and graduate students; we greatly value the undergraduate voice and seek submissions year-round.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Psi Chi Journal of Psychological Research</title>
      <URL>http://www.psichi.org/?page=journal_main</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The Psi Chi Journal of Psychological Research educates, supports, and promotes professional development, and disseminates psychological science. Psi Chi is the International Honor Society in Psychology.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The International Journal of Social Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://www.tijoss.com/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>TIJOSS is a peer-reviewed journal and papers are published on merit based after ‘blind’ peer review process by our experienced editorial board members. We publish both online and printed version of research papers in all fields of social sciences such as anthropology, archaeology, criminology, economics, education, history, linguistics, communication studies, political science and international relations, sociology, geography, law and psychology.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Research in Natural and Clinical Science and Technology (URNCST) Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www.urncst.com/</URL>
      <institution/>
      <description>The URNCST [pronounced “earnest”] Journal is an independent research journal based in Toronto, Canada that accepts research article submissions from undergraduate students all over the world. The URNCST Journal was created to provide dedicated undergraduate researchers with a cost-effective and meaningful platform to showcase their research findings, and prides itself on 8 defining characteristics: open access; peer-reviewed; rapid turnaround time; international; broad and multidisciplinary; indexed; innovative; and social media promoted. Furthermore, the URNCST Journal is unique among undergraduate research journals issuing all published articles a digital object identifier made possible through our CrossRef membership. To learn more and submit YOUR article, please visit https://www.urncst.com!</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Interstate - Journal of International Affairs</title>
      <URL>http://www.aber.ac.uk/en/interpol/current-students/undergraduate/interstate/</URL>
      <institution>Aberystwyth University</institution>
      <description>Founded in 1965 at Aberystwyth University's Department of International Politics, 'Interstate - Journal of International Affairs' is a student-run journal that focuses on international affairs.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>History Matters: An Undergraduate Journal of Historical Research</title>
      <URL>http://historymatters.appstate.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Appalachian State University </institution>
      <description>An undergraduate history journal, published annually on this website by the Department of History at Appalachian State University. The journal is edited by undergraduates with the help of a faculty board. Our goal is to publish the best undergraduate historical research possible. In doing so, we would like to provide an opportunity for top undergraduates from a variety of schools to be recognized for their work, familiarize them with the publishing process, and encourage student-faculty collaboration.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Impulse: An Undergraduate Journal for Neuroscience</title>
      <URL>http://impulse.appstate.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Appalachian State University </institution>
      <description>IMPULSE is the first international, online neuroscience journal for undergraduate publications. The journal is peer reviewed by students worldwide.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Armstrong Undergraduate Journal of History</title>
      <URL>https://digitalcommons.georgiasouthern.edu/aujh/</URL>
      <institution>Armstrong State University </institution>
      <description>Armstrong Undergraduate Journal of History is an online journal edited and produced by undergraduate students at Armstrong State University. The journal is dedicated to promoting undergraduate students’ research interest in history and their writing skills. The journal is also hoped to strengthen the collaborations in learning between undergraduates and graduates, students and faculty, and history majors and those from other study fields. All submissions will be fully refereed in a blind reviewing process by history professors and graduate students from Armstrong and other universities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>AUJUS: Auburn University Journal of Undergraduate Scholarship</title>
      <URL>http://www.auburn.edu/aujus</URL>
      <institution>Auburn University</institution>
      <description>AUJUS, the Auburn University Journal of Undergraduate Scholarship, is a faculty-refereed publication that showcases the research and scholarly accomplishments of Auburn University undergraduate students from any discipline.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Honors Review</title>
      <URL>http://honorsreview.wordpress.com/</URL>
      <institution>Augsburg College</institution>
      <description>A nationally competitive interdisciplinary journal seeking illuminating, insightful, and contemporary research at the undergraduate level. Students need not be members of Honors Programs to submit papers. The primary goal is to give all undergraduates the opportunity to participate in scholarly conversations within their disciplines and to expose them to the dialogue that occurs between a journal and a contributor in editing an article for publication. The Honors Review will provide its authors with the unique chance to receive prompt and personal feedback during the editing process through the use of private online discussion forums</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Arsenal</title>
      <URL>http://augusta.openrepository.com/augusta/handle/10675.2/561321</URL>
      <institution>Augusta University </institution>
      <description>The Arsenal (ISSN 2380-5064 online) is a peer-reviewed, open-access interdisciplinary publication that is committed to publishing manuscripts resulting from student research conducted at Augusta University. Each paper published in the Arsenal undergoes a peer review process facilitated by the journal‘s Editorial Review Board and must be approved by an appointed faculty reviewer in the paper’s respective discipline. The purpose of the journal is to promote and highlight the undergraduate research from a wide range of disciplines conducted at Augusta University; facilitate scholarly collaborations between students and faculty; and expose students to the publication and peer review process.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Digital Literature Review</title>
      <URL>http://bsu.edu/dlr</URL>
      <institution>Ball State University</institution>
      <description>Digital Literature Review is the Ball State University English Department's new undergraduate academic journal, edited and produced by Ball State undergraduates. Our goal is to showcase the valuable contributions of hardworking, creative undergraduate students. We welcome original, engaging, scholarly submissions from the perspective of a wide range of academic disciplines, including film studies, theatre, anthropology, psychology, and literary and cultural studies. Each issue is thematically driven, so please visit www.bsu.edu/dlr or email us at dlr@bsu.edu to find out more about our current focus.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Fine Focus</title>
      <URL>http://finefocus.org/</URL>
      <institution>Ball State University</institution>
      <description>As the first microbiology research journal for undergraduates, Fine Focus has an international Editorial Board composed of experts in all subdisciplines of microbiology, targeting undergraduate researchers and their mentors. It publishes original research by undergraduate students in microbiology. This includes works in all microbiological specialties, including microbiology education. Research in other biology disciplines will not be accepted unless the main emphasis of the work centers on microorganism(s). Submitted manuscripts go through a double-blind review process. If accepted, articles appear both in print and online. Fine Focus is managed entirely by undergraduate students from production to print; the Editorial Board reviews manuscripts.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Stance</title>
      <URL>https://www.stancephilosophy.com/</URL>
      <institution>Ball State University</institution>
      <description>Stance is an international philosophy journal published by Ball State University undergraduates. [ISSN 1943-1899] Beyond publishing manuscripts, we train an international external reviewer board. Stance is listed in The Philosopher's Index. All manuscript authors receive constructive feedback. 8% acceptance rate.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Scientia</title>
      <URL>http://issuu.com/baylor_scientia</URL>
      <institution>Baylor University</institution>
      <description>Scientia, established in 2014, is Baylor University's undergraduate research journal in science and technology. Scientia is a peer-reviewed journal and publishes original research, review articles, and abstracts written by Baylor undergraduates. With a new issue released each spring, Scientia highlights the research done by undergraduates in that year.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Beloit Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://burj.beloit.edu</URL>
      <institution>Beloit College</institution>
      <description>A student-run multidisciplinary research journal for Beloit College students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Alpenglow</title>
      <URL>https://orb.binghamton.edu/alpenglowjournal/</URL>
      <institution>Binghamton University</institution>
      <description>Alpenglow showcases and acknowledges the broad spectrum and quality of undergraduate student research, scholarly investigation, and creative work at Binghamton University. The journal accepts and publishes various formats of submissions of scholarly and creative work.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Al Noor</title>
      <URL>https://www.bcalnoor.org</URL>
      <institution>Boston College</institution>
      <description>Al Noor is Boston College's Middle Eastern Studies journal, based in Chestnut Hill, MA. It is run entirely by undergraduates at BC, features work from around the world, and is issued twice a year.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Elements</title>
      <URL>http://www.bc.edu/research/elements/</URL>
      <institution>Boston College</institution>
      <description>Elements was founded in September 2004 by a group of 20 undergraduate students. The journal published its first issue in May 2005, featuring research articles written by Boston College undergraduates along with shorter special features. The goal of the publication is to become a forum for the exchange of original ideas within and across disciplines at the university.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Butler Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.butler.edu/bjur/</URL>
      <institution>Butler University</institution>
      <description>The Butler Journal of Undergraduate Research publishes original, scholarly research undertaken by undergraduates from any college or university. BJUR builds upon and strengthens Butler’s commitment to quality undergraduate research by providing an outlet for the publication of outstanding undergraduate scholarship across the humanities, social and natural sciences.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Reach UR at Cal Poly Pomona</title>
      <URL>https://www.cpp.edu/~our-cpp/publications/journals.shtml</URL>
      <institution>Cal Poly Pomona</institution>
      <description>The Cal Poly Pomona Office of Undergraduate Research and Bronco Scholar at the University Library are proud to present Reach – Inspiring Creativity, Discovery, and Innovation, an online compilation of undergraduate research at Cal Poly Pomona. Reach showcases outstanding scholarship, creative works, and research conducted by undergraduate students under the mentorship of faculty members.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Caltech Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://curj.caltech.edu/</URL>
      <institution>California Institute of Technology</institution>
      <description>The Caltech Undergraduate Research Journal publishes the best undergraduate submissions from around the world in the form of scientific and featured articles.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The PUMP Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://math.csudh.edu/pumpjournal/index.php/pump</URL>
      <institution>California State University</institution>
      <description>A journal for research in mathematics done by undergraduate students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Culture, Society, and Praxis</title>
      <URL>https://digitalcommons.csumb.edu/csp/</URL>
      <institution>California State University, Monterey
                                                Bay</institution>
      <description>Culture, Society, and Praxis is a peer reviewed, undergraduate, open access social scientific journal. We accept all forms of scholarly expression, including research-based writing, creative writing, visual arts, and more. As long as it was created by a student and is relevant to the social sciences, we’d love to see it. We do not reject any eligible submissions; we simply ask that students commit to revising their work until it is publishable. You can check us out and submit work at www.culturesocietypraxis.com. For more information, contact Amanda Pullum, faculty advisor (apullum@csumb.edu).</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Epistimi</title>
      <URL>http://www.capital.edu/epistimi/</URL>
      <institution>Capital University</institution>
      <description>The mission of Epistimi: Capital University’s Undergraduate Research Journal is to highlight the empirical research conducted by Capital University students. Under the direction of student editors and a faculty editorial board, Epistimi is an extension of Capital University’s undergraduate research initiative, and it reflects Capital’s mission and goals.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>forsch! studentisches Online-Journal</title>
      <URL>http://openjournal.uni-oldenburg.de/index.php/forsch/index</URL>
      <institution>Carl von Ossietzky University Oldenburg</institution>
      <description>Das stu­den­ti­sche Online-Journal „forsch!" hat sich zum Ziel gesetzt, Bache­lor– und Master-Studierenden der Uni­ver­si­tät Olden­burg eine Platt­form für eigene wis­sen­schaft­li­che Arbei­ten bereit­zu­stel­len, um diese über den Kon­text einer Lehr­ver­an­stal­tung hin­aus nutz­bar zu machen. Damit ver­bun­den sol­len grund­le­gende Kom­pe­ten­zen, die zur Bil­dung einer Forscher_innen-Persönlichkeit bei­tra­gen, geför­dert werden.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Journal of Humanistic Studies</title>
      <URL>https://www.carleton.edu/ujhs/</URL>
      <institution>Carleton College</institution>
      <description>The Undergraduate Journal of Humanistic Studies (UJHS) is a peer-reviewed academic journal that promotes undergraduate research in the humanities and social sciences at Carleton College. Our goal is to present papers that bring to light new narratives and fresh points of view. Highlighting work that challenges dominant perspectives, the UJHS serves as a forum for contributors and readers to reconsider their position within the context of their society. In the spirit of the liberal arts, the UJHS is a multidisciplinary journal that accepts submissions from a broad range of subjects, demonstrating how student research can contribute to a variety of fields.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Carthage Vanguard</title>
      <URL>https://www.carthage.edu/vanguard/</URL>
      <institution>Carthage College</institution>
      <description>The Vanguard is Carthage’s very own student-written, -edited, and -published multidisciplinary undergraduate research journal. The Carthage Vanguard accepts submissions from all disciplines and in a variety of discipline-specific formats. Please visit our Submission Guidelines for additional information on submitting your material to the Vanguard. To submit your material to the Vanguard staff, or to request additional information about our journal, please contact us via email, research@carthage.edu.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Discussions</title>
      <URL>https://discussionsjournal.com/</URL>
      <institution>Case Western Reserve University</institution>
      <description>Discussions is the undergraduate research journal of Case Western Reserve University in Cleveland, OH. We are currently accepting submissions from all majors! We accept from all over the nation and have received submissions from Princeton, Florida, and even New Zealand. Our current acceptance rates are around 30 percent, and we are becoming more competitive every year. Check out our website to learn more!</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Reuleaux: The Mines Undergraduate Research Magazine</title>
      <URL>https://www.mines.edu/undergraduate-research/reuleaux/</URL>
      <institution>Chicago School of Mines</institution>
      <description>Reuleaux is a peer-edited magazine produced by and for students at the Colorado School of Mines.This magazine gives undergraduate researchers a platform by which they may publish engaging narrative descriptions of their research — in the physical sciences or otherwise — that are approachable to a large audience.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>SURJ at Clark University</title>
      <URL>http://www.surjatclarku.com/</URL>
      <institution>Clark University</institution>
      <description>Scholarly Undergraduate Research Journal is Clark University's first undergraduate interdisciplinary research journal. It is student-run and peer-reviewed. SURJ seeks to highlight the quality of research produced by Clark undergraduates and provide undergraduates with important experience in academic publishing. The SURJ editorial board can be reached at surj@clarku.edu ISSN 2472-677X (print) ISSN 2472-6788 (online)</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Research and Scholarly Excellence</title>
      <URL>http://jur.colostate.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Colorado State University </institution>
      <description>JUR is a peer-reviewed, undergraduate journal registered with the Library of Congress that accepts submissions of any subject, from any undergraduate institution.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>El Río: A Student Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://ojs.csupueblo.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Colorado State University-Pueblo</institution>
      <description>El Río: A Student Research Journal is a student-run research journal at CSU-Pueblo that focuses on outstanding student work from the humanities, behavioral, social, natural, and health and applied sciences. Its mission is to acknowledge, promote, and disseminate high-quality student research that shapes discourse and fosters understanding.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Columbia Economics Review</title>
      <URL>http://columbiaeconreview.com/</URL>
      <institution>Columbia University</institution>
      <description>Founded in 2009 as the first undergraduate economics journal in the United States, the Columbia Economics Review (CER) aims to promote discourse and research at the intersection of economics, business, politics, and society by publishing a rigorous selection of student essays, opinions, and research papers in a print journal released each semester. We further strive to engage individuals on campus, locally, and globally through speaker series, symposia, competitions, and other events established to promote dialogue and encourage deeper insights on economic issues. CER is sponsored by the Program for Economic Research at Columbia University and the Institute for Social and Economic Research and Policy. CER is entirely led, organized, and operated by undergraduate students at Columbia across a multitude of academic disciplines.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Consilience, The Journal of Sustainability Development</title>
      <URL>http://www.consiliencejournal.org/</URL>
      <institution>Columbia University</institution>
      <description>Consilience is an online journal dedicated to promoting interdisciplinary dialogue on sustainable development. This journal aims to bring students, researchers, professors, and practitioners from a variety of disciplines and geographical regions in direct conversation with each other through an online, academically rigorous medium. Consilience publishes scholarly articles, opinion pieces, field notes, editorial columns, and photo essays. By providing a public platform for discussion, we hope to encourage a global community to think more broadly, thoroughly, and analytically about sustainable development. The journal is run by a team of undergraduate and graduate students, under the guidance of faculty from Columbia University in the City of New York.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Politics and Society</title>
      <URL>http://www.helvidius.org/</URL>
      <institution>Columbia University</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Politics &amp; Society focuses on undergraduates and interdisciplinary coverage of public policy and law. This journal is the only scholarly publication of its kind. It is also commercially distributed nationwide.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Morningside Review</title>
      <URL>http://morningsidereview.org</URL>
      <institution>Columbia University</institution>
      <description>The Morningside Review is an online journal published by Undergraduate Writing Program at Columbia University. It features exemplary essays written by first-year undergraduates in the Core Curriculum course, University Writing. Hundreds of students voluntarily submit their essays to TMR for possible publication and approximately ten are chosen each year by an editorial advisory board made up of University Writing instructors. Since these essays serve as vivid examples of peer work, they are commonly assigned in University Writing. Students may be prompted by their instructors to identify the rhetorical strategies employed in an essay, contemplate their effectiveness, and attempt to emulate those they admire in their own work. Thus, Columbia University students may make their imprint on University Writing long after they have completed the course.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Columbia Undergraduate Journal of History</title>
      <URL>http://cujh.columbia.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Columbia University </institution>
      <description>The Columbia Undergraduate Journal of History is a publication of the Undergraduate History Council at Columbia University. To solicit material, the Undergraduate History Council asks professors from history departments across the United States and internationally to nominate the most outstanding undergraduate work from their classes. They post all nominated articles and then select from among them to be published in the journal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Columbia Undergraduate Science Journal</title>
      <URL>http://cusj.columbia.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Columbia University </institution>
      <description>The Columbia Undergraduate Science Journal is a peer-reviewed, professional-level, open-access, academic publication that is committed to publishing manuscripts of the highest scholarship resulting from significant scientific research or outstanding scientific analysis. Each paper published in the CUSJ undergoes a double-blind peer-review process facilitated by the journal's Editorial Review Board and a faculty review by a member of the Faculty Advisory Board. The CUSJ has two primary goals. First, the CUSJ aims to (1) publish works of the highest scholarship authored primarily by undergraduates. Second, the CUSJ aims to (2) educate students about the academic publication process, both from the inside as a member of the CUSJ staff and from the outside as a submitter to a scientific journal with academic standards that are as rigorous as any professional-level scientific publication.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Momentum</title>
      <URL>http://momentum.columbusstate.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Columbus State University</institution>
      <description>Momentum advocates the presence of a diverse student population conducting independent studies. It serves as a platform to promote creativity, inquiry, and intellectual critique among undergraduates from all disciplines. Led by an Editorial Advisory Board, the journal conforms to the highest levels of academic honor by utilizing a blind review process that permits erudite submission from students across the disciplines. The journal's ultimate goal is to publish scholarly research among a wide range of captivating themes. Momentum accepts perspectives, creative inquires, and quantitative and qualitative research at the undergraduate level. Please email the Momentum editorial board at momentum@columbusstate.edu.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Metamorphosis</title>
      <URL>https://metamorphosis.coplac.org/index.php/metamorphosis</URL>
      <institution>Council of Public Liberal Arts Colleges</institution>
      <description>Metamorphosis features scholarly and creative work at COPLAC member institutions across the United States and Canada. The journal is interdisciplinary by design, highlighting work in the natural sciences, social sciences, humanities, arts and professional programs.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>DUJS Homepage</title>
      <URL>http://dujs.dartmouth.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Dartmouth College</institution>
      <description>Founded in 1998, the Dartmouth Undergraduate Journal of Science aims to increase scientific awareness by providing an interdisciplinary forum for sharing undergraduate research and enriching scientific knowledge. The DUJS prints quarterly journals that include science news and review articles, along with research by undergraduates. Weekly Dartmouth Science News articles are also posted to the DUJS website.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>DePaul Discoveries</title>
      <URL>http://via.library.depaul.edu/depaul-disc/</URL>
      <institution>DePaul University College of Science and
                                                Health</institution>
      <description>DePaul Discoveries is a peer-reviewed undergraduate research journal published by DePaul University’s College of Science and Health.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>DUJOUR (Dillard University Journal of Undergraduate Research)</title>
      <URL>http://www.dillard.edu/images/stories/food/dujourfall2010.pdf</URL>
      <institution>Dillard University</institution>
      <description>DUJOUR (Dillard University Journal of Undergraduate Research) highlights student research and creative work, advances independent undergraduate scholarship, and brings research to the forefront of undergradute student awareness.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Drew Review</title>
      <URL>https://www.drew.edu/library/special-collections-archives/university-archives/drewpubs/</URL>
      <institution>Drew University</institution>
      <description>We are an undergraduate research journal based at Drew University in northern New Jersey.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Kentucky Journal of Undergraduate Scholarship</title>
      <URL>http://encompass.eku.edu/kjus/</URL>
      <institution>Eastern Kentucky University</institution>
      <description>The Kentucky Journal of Undergraduate Scholarship is an online, refereed journal dedicated to showcasing the research and creative activities of undergraduate students across Kentucky. Submissions are invited throughout the year from a variety of disciplines. The journal publishes annually.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Elon Journal of Undergraduate Research in Communications</title>
      <URL>http://www.elon.edu/e-web/academics/communications/research/</URL>
      <institution>Elon University </institution>
      <description>The Elon Journal is the only journal with a focus on undergraduate research in journalism, media, and communications.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Perspectives on Undergraduate Research and Mentoring</title>
      <URL>http://blogs.elon.edu/purm/</URL>
      <institution>Elon University </institution>
      <description>Perspectives on Undergraduate Research and Mentoring (PURM) is an open, multidisciplinary, peer-reviewed online journal supporting the mission of undergraduate research and the programs that strive to provide undergraduate students opportunities to participate in scholarly activities with faculty mentors.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Issues in Politcal Economy</title>
      <URL>http://www.elon.edu/e-web/students/ipe/default.xhtml</URL>
      <institution>Elon University &amp; Mary Washington University
                                            </institution>
      <description>Issues in Political Economy is a student run journal whose focus is to promote undergraduate research in all areas of economics.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Emory Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://scholarblogs.emory.edu/eurj/</URL>
      <institution>Emory University</institution>
      <description>Founded in spring 2005, EURJ chronicles the research achievements of Emory University undergraduates. In addition, the journal provides insight on research opportunities, events, and issues affecting research at Emory and beyond. EURJ is a multidisciplinary journal and accepts material from any area of interest as long as it meets the standards set forth by the journal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of European Psychology Students</title>
      <URL>http://jeps.efpsa.org/</URL>
      <institution>European Federation of Psychology Students'
                                                Association</institution>
      <description>The Journal of European Psychology Students (JEPS) is an open-access, double-blind, peer-reviewed journal for psychology students worldwide. JEPS is run by highly motivated European psychology students and has been publishing since 2009. By ensuring that authors are always provided with extensive feedback, JEPS gives psychology students the chance to gain experience in publishing and to improve their scientific skills. Furthermore, JEPS provides students with the opportunity to share their research and to take a first step toward a scientific career.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Journal of Global Citizenship</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.fairfield.edu/jogc/</URL>
      <institution>Fairfield University </institution>
      <description>With the help of Fairfield University’s International Studies Program, four undergraduate students established the Undergraduate Journal of Global Citizenship in 2010. The journal was part of an AAC&amp;U Bringing Theory to Practice grant to promote responsible global citizenship and student development. The journal is designed to highlight the accomplishments of young minds in constant intellectual engagement with their surroundings. The Undergraduate Journal of Global Citizenship honors the work of undergraduates from diverse academic backgrounds, united by their dedication to global citizenship and social responsibility, in line with the Jesuit values of the university. Welcomed are undergraduate submissions that showcase and promote the understanding of global citizenship and social responsibility. We view global citizenship as a disengagement from barriers into a recognition and understanding of human actions with social, political, environmental, and/or economic impact worldwide. A sense of community, not only with our direct neighbors but also with societies and lives around the globe, makes a socially responsible individual.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Psychology and Behavioral Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://view.fdu.edu/default.aspx?id=784</URL>
      <institution>Fairleigh Dickinson University</institution>
      <description>JPBS is an annual periodical published by the Psychology and Counseling Department of Fairleigh Dickinson University at Madison, New Jersey.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>FAU Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://journals.fcla.edu/faurj</URL>
      <institution>Florida Atlantic University</institution>
      <description>The Florida Atlantic Undergraduate Research Journal (FAURJ) is an interdisciplinary, peer-reviewed journal that is published annually. The FAURJ is published online and in print. Its missions are to showcase high quality undergraduate research in all fields, supply younger students with an idea of the standard of research, and promote inquiry-based activities at FAU.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Aquila: The FGCU Student Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www2.fgcu.edu/Aquila/index.html</URL>
      <institution>Florida Gulf Coast University</institution>
      <description>Aquila - The FGCU Student Research Journal publishes exceptional student scholarship from all academic disciplines and levels of study at Florida Gulf Coast University. This open-access journal is published twice annually in both print and online mediums.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Owl at FSU</title>
      <URL>https://journals.flvc.org/owl/index</URL>
      <institution>Florida State University</institution>
      <description>The Owl is an interdisciplinary journal that publishes a variety of undergraduate research at Florida State University, as well as creative projects such as artwork, photography, poetry, and creative writing. It promotes an interdisciplinary exchange of ideas, showcases the heterogeneity of our emerging scholars, and establishes undergraduate research as a focus of Florida State's academic community.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Fordham Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.fordham.edu/academics/colleges__graduate_s/undergraduate_colleg/fordham_college_at_r/undergraduate_resear/the_fordham_undergra/</URL>
      <institution>Fordham University </institution>
      <description>The Fordham Undergraduate Research Journal is a student-run journal that features high quality, peer-reviewed, original research conducted by undergraduate students in the sciences, humanities, and social sciences. The journal welcomes submissions from current Fordham students and recent graduates as well as students from other universities who conducted research at Fordham.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Academic Leadership Journal in Student Research</title>
      <URL>https://scholars.fhsu.edu/aljsr/</URL>
      <institution>Fort Hays State University</institution>
      <description>Academic Leadership Journal in Student Research is an Open Access, annual, online, peer reviewed, international journal dedicated to the publication of student research (undergraduate and graduate) within all disciplines and of pedagogically based professional work that explores the intersection of student research with teaching and faculty research. Our mission is to provide a forum for exceptional student research and to promote collaboration between students and teachers in the classroom, laboratory, and field.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>George Mason Review</title>
      <URL>http://gmreview.gmu.edu</URL>
      <institution>George Mason University</institution>
      <description>The George Mason Review is a cross-disciplinary undergraduate journal. Through the publication of exemplary, scholarly works, the GMR acts as a medium for discussion among us--the Mason undergraduate body--about scholarship. It seeks to re-vision scholarship by exploring and challenging the boundaries separating disciplines from each other, the humanities from the sciences, and academic from creative. In doing so, the GMR hopes to represent the academic excellence of the Mason undergraduate body.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://undergraduateresearch.org/</URL>
      <institution>Georgia College &amp; State University</institution>
      <description>Undergraduate Research is a national double-blind, educator-reviewed print and electronic journal published annually in the winter. The journal is a forum for multidisciplinary undergraduate research and creative endeavors within higher education such as case studies, conceptual pieces, creative endeavors, creative writing, journalism writings, literature reviews, original art, photography, and scientific studies.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Corinthian</title>
      <URL>https://corinthian.gcsu.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Georgia College and State University</institution>
      <description>This scholarly journal, published every spring, recognizes student achievement in research by providing publishing opportunities for undergraduate and graduate GC students from all disciplines.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Discovery: Georgia State University Honors College Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://scholarworks.gsu.edu/discovery/</URL>
      <institution>Georgia State University</institution>
      <description>DISCOVERY is an undergraduate research journal featuring publications from students enrolled in the Honors College at Georgia State University. The mission of DISCOVERY, subtitled The Honors College Undergraduate Research Journal, is to promote, showcase, and disseminate original scholarship from all disciplines conducted by Honors College undergraduate students who have been involved in faculty-mentored research projects and creative activities. DISCOVERY promotes, encourages and rewards undergraduate research excellence and provides opportunities for the exchange of ideas beyond the classroom.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Gettysburg College Journal of the Civil War Era</title>
      <URL>http://cupola.gettysburg.edu/gcjcwe/</URL>
      <institution>Gettysburg College</institution>
      <description>The Gettysburg College Journal of the Civil War Era annually publishes undergraduate papers on the Civil War era and its lasting memory. We are interested in academic essays, public history essays, and book reviews broadly relating to the American Civil War.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Gettysburg Historical Journal</title>
      <URL>http://cupola.gettysburg.edu/ghj/</URL>
      <institution>Gettysburg College</institution>
      <description>The Gettysburg Historical Journal features original undergraduate student research and essays. It is produced by students at Gettysburg College and published annually. While the Gettysburg Historical Journal focuses on research in the field of history, we publish and encourage submissions from other disciplines that utilize historical viewpoints or methodologies, including sociology, anthropology, and classics.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Mercury: The Student Art &amp; Literary Magazine of Gettysburg College</title>
      <URL>http://cupola.gettysburg.edu/mercury/</URL>
      <institution>Gettysburg College</institution>
      <description>The Mercury: The Student Art &amp; Literary Magazine of Gettysburg College has been published annually since 1894. All students of the College are invited to participate and submit their work. Student editors are elected annually by the entire staff. The Mercury accepts submissions of fiction, nonfiction, poetry, artwork, and photography.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Grand Valley Journal of History</title>
      <URL>http://scholarworks.gvsu.edu/gvjh/</URL>
      <institution>Grand Valley State University</institution>
      <description>The Grand Valley Journal of History provides undergraduate students from all institutions with an opportunity to publish their historically-based research. The GVJH is a journal for all majors, operated by student editors and overseen by a faculty advisory board.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Harvard Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.thurj.org</URL>
      <institution>Harvard University</institution>
      <description/>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://www.hcs.harvard.edu/~jus/home.html</URL>
      <institution>Harvard University </institution>
      <description>The Journal of Undergraduate Sciences is the nation's premiere peer-reviewed scientific journal dedicated to original research done by undergraduates and high school students. Written and published by students for students, the journal publishes articles in fields ranging from astronomy to zoology. As a collaborative effort among undergraduates, graduate students, and professors, JUS is a forum in which students can participate in the frontiers of science and become acquainted with the important scientific issues. Additionally, JUS encourages undergraduates to gain valuable experience by communicating their research to an audience of peers. Through its activities, JUS seeks to vitalize interest in science and its many implications for society.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Texas State Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://journals.tdl.org/txstate/index.php/txstate</URL>
      <institution>Honors College Texas State University</institution>
      <description>Every year Texas State Publishes an Undergraduate Research Journal. Use the link to submit your research for publication!</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Grassroots Writing Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://isuwriting.com/grassroots/</URL>
      <institution>Illinois State University</institution>
      <description>The Grassroots Writing Research Journal is produced twice each year by the Writing Program at Illinois State University. The print issue of each journal is used as a primary text in two of ISU's undergraduate general education writing courses. Digital versions of previous issues are available online. The title of the journal reflects our aspirations—to present writing research by different authors and in a wide range of different topics, forms, and media. The journal solicits authors from within and outside of our institutions and other academic institutions. We've published faculty, graduate students, undergraduates, high school students, and nonstudents-- all Writing researchers. We encourage authors to share not only what they’ve learned about writing but also how they learned it. Thus, each new volume brings together a diverse collection of articles that all enact some form of writing research from a variety of authors. Authors can learn more about publishing on our websites, which offer both back issues of the journal and a range of different guides for researching and writing for the journal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Journal, Illinois Tech</title>
      <URL>http://urj.library.iit.edu/index.php/urj</URL>
      <institution>Illinois Tech</institution>
      <description>The IIT Undergraduate Research Journal is a student-led, peer-reviewed, scientific journal published by undergraduates for undergraduates and the IIT academic community at large.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Economic Review</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.iwu.edu/uer/</URL>
      <institution>Illinois Wesleyan University </institution>
      <description>The Undergraduate Economic Review is an online peer-reviewed journal that promotes undergraduate economic research from around the world.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Indiana University Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://iujur.iu.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Indiana University</institution>
      <description>The IU Journal of Undergraduate Research is an annual, open access journal published through IUScholarWorks.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www.iusb.edu/ugr-journal/</URL>
      <institution>Indiana University South Bend</institution>
      <description>The Indiana University Undergraduate Research Journal is a refereed journal of outstanding scholarship featuring the work of IU South Bend students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>SPORA</title>
      <URL>http://www.sporajournal.org/</URL>
      <institution>Intercollegiate Biomathematics Alliance</institution>
      <description>Spora: A Journal of Biomathematics, a nexus of undergraduate research, is dedicated to further the field of biomathematics and the development of future scientists in mathematical biology. Spora is fully refereed and published both online and in-print.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>James Madison Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.jmu.edu/jmurj/index.shtml</URL>
      <institution>James Madison University</institution>
      <description>The James Madison Undergraduate Research Journal (JMURJ) is a multidisciplinary, peer-reviewed journal produced by a student editorial board working alongside faculty reviewers. This online journal publishes excellent scholarly research conducted by JMU undergraduates from all academic disciplines. Submissions are evaluated and published on a rolling basis.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Rhet Tech Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www.jmu.edu/wrtc/students/undergraduate/rhet-tech.shtml</URL>
      <institution>James Madison University </institution>
      <description>RhetTech—founded at James Madison University by the School of Writing, Rhetoric, and Technical Communication in 2017—is a revamp of JMU’s longtime online journal for work generated in university writing courses. RhetTech showcases exemplary work being done in undergraduate writing, rhetoric, and technical communication courses around the country. This journal is run by young scholars in JMU’s School of Writing, Rhetoric and Technical Communication. The name ‘RhetTech’ refers to the genres of works accepted by the journal: ‘Rhet’ refers to Rhetoric, and ‘Tech’ refers to Technical Communication. We accept a variety of content, including: text-based essays, videos, podcasts, photo essays, reviews, websites, blogs, and many more. We encourage student writers to utilize all of the tools at their disposal to communicate the messages they wish to share with readers.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Crossing Borders: A Multidisciplinary Journal of Undergraduate Scholarship</title>
      <URL>http://newprairiepress.org/crossingborders/</URL>
      <institution>Kansas State University</institution>
      <description>Crossing Borders introduces undergraduates to the processes and values of open-access, peer-reviewed communication, thereby preparing them to be more critical consumers and producers of scholarly discourse. The editors welcome submissions from any discipline.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Live Ideas: Undergraduate Primary Texts Journal</title>
      <URL>https://liveideasjournal.org/</URL>
      <institution>Kansas State University</institution>
      <description>Live Ideas is the open-access, peer-reviewed undergraduate journal of Kansas State University’s Primary Texts Certificate program. It is co-produced by students and faculty at K-State and is published online once per semester.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Journal for the Human Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://www.kon.org/urc/urc_research_journal.html</URL>
      <institution>Kappa Omicron Nu</institution>
      <description>This journal was organized as a refereed publication during the First Undergraduate Research Conference of the Undergraduate Research Community (URC) for the Human Sciences at the Kappa Omicron Nu Conclave, Grosvenor Resort, Orlando, August 2-5, 2001.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Kennesaw Tower</title>
      <URL>http://kennesawtower.kennesaw.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Kennesaw State University</institution>
      <description>The Kennesaw Tower is an undergraduate research journal affiliated with and based in the Department of Foreign Languages at Kennesaw State University. Our mission is the diffusion and participation of quality, undergraduate research projects in Chinese, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, and Spanish into the regional, national and international arena through an on-line medium.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Valley Humanities Review</title>
      <URL>http://www.lvc.edu/vhr/</URL>
      <institution>Lebanon Valley College</institution>
      <description>The Valley Humanities Review is an online journal devoted to undergraduate research in the humanities. It publishes one issue each spring and runs two annual contests with $500 prizes: a competition for high school students and one for LVC students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Lethbridge Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.lurj.org/</URL>
      <institution>Lethbridge University </institution>
      <description>The Lethbridge Undergraduate Research Journal is an online journal in which undergraduate students can publish their academic papers. It is run by and for undergraduate students. The L.U.R.J. is international in scope and welcomes papers from all undergraduates. Papers are accepted at all times. New issues are released approximately every 4 months.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Journal of Teaching &amp; Research</title>
      <URL>https://www.lsuajournal.org/</URL>
      <institution>Louisiana State University of Alexandria</institution>
      <description>The LSUA Undergraduate Journal of Teaching and Research (UJTR) is an open-access, peer-reviewed journal designed to acknowledge the achievements of LSUA undergraduates in all areas of teaching and research. While undergraduate teaching and research are the main focus, research from faculty members is also encouraged for submission. While we primarily accept publications within the LSUA community, we also welcome submissions outside of LSUA.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>First-Gen Voices</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.lmu.edu/fgv/</URL>
      <institution>Loyola Marymount University </institution>
      <description>First-Gen Voices: Creative and Critical Narratives on the First-Generation College Experience is a peer-reviewed journal of creative writing, visual and recorded art, and scholarly work from the first-generation college community---students, faculty, and staff whose parents have not completed bachelor's degrees from institutions in the United States). Founded in spring 2014 at Loyola Marymount University, First-Gen Voices offers a space where individuals from diverse backgrounds can engage one another in conversation through their shared social identity as first-gen college students. This publication aims to promote awareness about the first-gen experience, the valuable forms of social capital first-gen students bring into the university, and the meaningful contributions they make to their local and global communities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>MIT Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://murj.mit.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Massachusetts Institute of Technology</institution>
      <description>The MIT Undergraduate Research Journal (MURJ) is MIT's only peer-reviewed scientific journal serving the undergraduate population.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Harf: A Journal of South Asian Studies</title>
      <URL>http://www.facebook.com/harfjournal</URL>
      <institution>McGill University</institution>
      <description>Harf: A Journal of South Asian Studies invites academic work from undergraduate and graduate students working on South Asia. We are a new journal published out of McGill University in Montreal. We welcome all submissions pertaining to the anthropology, history, literatures, and religions of South Asia. We are interested, particularly, in essays that explore marginalized voices, communities, practices, and concepts. Submissions must be double-spaced and 15-30 pages in length, inclusive of all endnotes, footnotes, and bibliography. Submissions must be formatted according to the Chicago Manual of Style as per the notes and bibliography system. Queries may be sent to harfjournal@gmail.com or via our Facebook page: www.facebook.com/harfjournal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Graduate Journal of Mathematics</title>
      <URL>https://www.gradmath.org/</URL>
      <institution>Mediterranean Institute for the Mathematical
                                                Sciences</institution>
      <description>The Graduate Journal of Mathematics is a journal that publishes original work as well as expository work of general mathematical interest which add to the literature, have pedagogical value and help make more widely accessible significant mathematical ideas, constructions or theorems.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Mapping Politics</title>
      <URL>http://www.mappingpolitics.ca/</URL>
      <institution>Memorial University of Newfoundland</institution>
      <description>Mapping Politics is an annual peer-reviewed journal produced by students in the Political Science department at Memorial University in St. John's, Newfoundland. We welcome submissions from Memorial students in all areas of political science including Newfoundland and Labrador politics, Canadian politics, international relations, media and politics, comparative politics, and political theory.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>ReCUR (Red Cedar Undergraduate Research)</title>
      <URL>http://www.recur.msu.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Michigan State University </institution>
      <description>ReCUR is an annual publication of the Michigan State University Honors College that highlights the diversity and quality of its students’ research and creative endeavors.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Knighted: An Interdisciplinary Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://www.mga.edu/knowledgeatwork/knighted-journal.aspx</URL>
      <institution>Middle Georgia State University</institution>
      <description>Knighted: An Interdisciplinary Journal of Undergraduate Research seeks to highlight the diverse array of fine undergraduate work being done across a wide variety of disciplines at Middle Georgia State University. The University’s mission statement calls attention to “lifelong learners whose scholarship and careers enhance the region,” and we believe that Knighted does precisely that by providing a public venue for students to demonstrate their research skills.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Scientia et Humanitas</title>
      <URL>http://capone.mtsu.edu/scientia/ojs/index.php/seth</URL>
      <institution>Middle Tennessee State University </institution>
      <description>from the natural and social sciences and from the humanities from Middle Tennessee State University students and recent graduates either by themselves or in conjunction with a faculty mentor. The journal is a peer-reviewed publication of the University Honors College.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Merge : The W's Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.muw.edu/honors/merge</URL>
      <institution>Mississippi University for women</institution>
      <description>Merge is a multidisciplinary university-wide undergraduate research publication. Submissions are accepted and encouraged from students across the university. Our purpose is to promote quality research from students of every academic discipline and level by giving them a platform for sharing their research.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>LOGOS: A Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://www.missouristate.edu/logos/default.htm</URL>
      <institution>Missouri State University</institution>
      <description>LOGOS: A Journal of Undergraduate Research is dedicated to publishing outstanding work by undergraduates in every academic discipline, including original research, essays, creative writing, and artwork. Led by Honors College student editors and advised by a Faculty Advisory Board, LOGOS conforms to the highest standards of scholastic integrity in a blind peer-review process.The Editorial Board welcomes submissions from current and former undergraduate students and collaborative teams, particularly those engaged in departmental honors work, independent study, research assistance, or a competitive summer fellowship.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>National Undergraduate Research Clearinghouse</title>
      <URL>http://www.webclearinghouse.net/</URL>
      <institution>Missouri Western State University</institution>
      <description>The Clearinghouse is an online journal for undergraduates in any STEM fields (Science Technology Engineering and Math) discipline to disseminate their research.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Reinvention: an International Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://www2.warwick.ac.uk/fac/cross_fac/iatl/reinvention/</URL>
      <institution>Monash University &amp; The University of
                                                Warwick</institution>
      <description>Reinvention: a Journal of Undergraduate Research is a new, online, peer-reviewed journal dedicated to the publication of high-quality undergraduate student research. The journal welcomes academic articles from all disciplinary areas. All articles in this journal undergo rigorous peer review, based on initial editor screening and refereeing by two anonymous referees. The journal is produced, edited, and managed by students and staff at Monash University and the University of Warwick. It is published biannually and only houses papers written by undergraduate students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Midwest Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://research.monm.edu/mjur</URL>
      <institution>Monmouth College</institution>
      <description>The Midwest Journal of Undergraduate Research is an academic peer-reviewed journal, produced under the direction of student editors and a faculty advisory board. Founded in 2011, the MJUR is dedicated to the publication of outstanding scholarship by undergraduates. The journal accepts submissions of research and analysis from all academic disciplines. Although the majority of manuscripts are submitted by students from colleges and universities in the U.S. Midwest, there is no regional restriction on submissions. Acceptance rate averages 25%. Please visit the MJUR website for more information and instructions for manuscript submission.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Scholars' Day Review</title>
      <URL>http://web.monroecc.edu/manila/webfiles/scholarsday/SDR.html</URL>
      <institution>Monroe Community College, Rochester, NY</institution>
      <description>SCHOLARS' DAY REVIEW is a faculty-juried journal showcasing the exceptional presentation papers of student scholars who participated in Monroe Community College's Scholars' Day.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Young Scholars in Writing</title>
      <URL>http://arc.lib.montana.edu/ojs/index.php/Young-Scholars-In-Writing/index</URL>
      <institution>Montana State University </institution>
      <description>Young Scholars in Writing: Undergraduate Research in Writing and Rhetoric (YSW) is the first international undergraduate research journal in rhetoric and writing studies and has garnered a national reputation in its fields. Articles are indexed by major databases (EBSCO, CompPile), cited by the field's researchers, and reprinted in collections of the field's work.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UReCA</title>
      <URL>http://www.nchc-ureca.com</URL>
      <institution>National Collegiate Honors Council</institution>
      <description>UReCA, the NCHC Web journal of Undergraduate Research and Creative Activity, is seeking submissions from all currently enrolled undergraduate students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Aeolus</title>
      <URL>https://aeolus.scholasticahq.com/</URL>
      <institution>New College of Florida</institution>
      <description>An interdisciplinary, undergraduate run, faculty-sponsored, peer-reviewed publication showcasing student research.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>NYU American Public Policy Review</title>
      <URL>https://nyuappr.pubpub.org/</URL>
      <institution>New York University</institution>
      <description>The NYU American Public Policy Review (ISSN 2693-9797) is a biannual publication of scholarly articles from undergraduate and graduate students that propose bold, original ideas for change within local, state, or federal government in the United States. The journal is published by undergraduate students at New York University, and submissions are peer-reviewed by faculty with relevant expertise from institutions across the United States. Submissions are open to undergraduate and graduate students from any accredited higher education institution.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Interdependent: Journal of Undergraduate Research in Global Studies</title>
      <URL>https://wp.nyu.edu/interdependent/</URL>
      <institution>New York University</institution>
      <description>The Interdependent is committed to exploring the global commons across the sciences, social sciences, and humanities. Its mission is to foster multidisciplinary research and discussion on global interdependence and cross-cultural encounters, and to encourage global empathy. It publishes third-year global travel reflections, as well as shortened fourth-year theses and creative works across all concentrations in NYU's Global Liberal Studies program.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Illuminate: The Undergraduate Journal of the Northeast Regional Honors Council</title>
      <URL>https://www.illuminatenrhc.com/</URL>
      <institution>Northeast Regional Honors Council</institution>
      <description>Illuminate features academic and creative content of honors students from the Northeast region.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Compass: An Undergraduate Journal of American Political Ideas</title>
      <URL>https://compassjournal.org/</URL>
      <institution>Northern Illinois University</institution>
      <description>Compass: An Undergraduate Journal of American Political Ideas seeks to publish essays by undergraduates at colleges and universities anywhere in the world on current American political issues understood in the broad contexts of political philosophy, history, literature, and culture. The journal encourages submissions from across academic disciplines and welcomes the use of various historical, philosophic, and empirical methods of analysis. This online journal aims to provide a space for the work of talented undergraduates who have original and well-articulated insights on important ideas and issues relating to American democracy. Please submit your essays to compass@startingpointsjournal.com. Published essays will usually be 1500-2000 words in length. We encourage a lively style that is highly readable. This is a venue to relate original work, whether using interpretive textual analysis, archival work, quantitative findings, comparative historical analysis, or other methodological approaches. However, we ask that these findings not be delivered or expressed in the manner of a term paper to specialist professors but in a more journalistic fashion to a wider audience of readers eager to glean what's interesting from your findings. Once you have submitted your essay, the editorial team will work quickly to let you know if your piece will be appropriate for this journal and whether it requires revisions. Compass is a project of the Tocqueville Forum at Northern Illinois University, in partnership with Starting Points: A Journal of American Principles and American Practices, a project of the Kinder Institute at University of Missouri.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Nýsa: The NKU Journal of Student Research</title>
      <URL>https://inside.nku.edu/gero/isrca/nku-student-journals/Journal.html</URL>
      <institution>Northern Kentucky University</institution>
      <description>Nýsa seeks to publish the best of undergraduate and student research from NKU. It provides an outlet for outstanding contributions from students in all fields, with special emphases on fields lacking in discipline-specific venues, research that spans several disciplines, and research that is smaller in scope but still tells a complete story.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Northwestern Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.thenurj.com/</URL>
      <institution>Northwestern University</institution>
      <description>The Northwestern Undergraduate Research Journal (NURJ) is a student-produced journal that showcases select research done by Northwestern undergraduates from a variety of academic backgrounds. We publish everything from research in mechanical engineering to anthropology to biological sciences to history. NURJ’s mission is to bring awareness to the Northwestern community about the outstanding research being accomplished by undergraduate students as well as the research opportunities available to Northwestern students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>On Second Thought</title>
      <URL>https://oberlinost.wordpress.com/</URL>
      <institution>Oberlin College</institution>
      <description>As Oberlin College’s alternative history journal, On Second Thought publishes innovative, accessible, and engaging historical content with the goal of reaching the Oberlin community and beyond.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Critical Theory and Social Justice Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://scholar.oxy.edu/ctsj/</URL>
      <institution>Occidental College</institution>
      <description>CTSJ is dedicated to providing a forum for undergraduate students to develop and share critical research and writing on the intersections of "race," "sexuality," and "nationality" as they relate to problems of social justice. The journal seeks to foster exchange of ideas across disciplines and deepen understandings of systems of injustice, and in this way advances the mission of Occidental College: to develop critical, thoughtful, and active participation in an increasingly pluralistic and conflict-ridden global culture.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>International Journal of Undergraduate Research and Creative Activities</title>
      <URL>http://commons.pacificu.edu/ijurca/</URL>
      <institution>Pacific University </institution>
      <description>A peer-reviewed, open-access journal dedicated to the publication of outstanding scholarship by undergraduates and their mentors from academic institutions of higher learning. The journal accepts submissions of research articles, fiction, poetry, photography, videos, and other creative works from undergraduate students in all academic disciplines.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Journal of Service Learning and Community-Based Research</title>
      <URL>https://berks.psu.edu/undergraduate-journal</URL>
      <institution>Penn State Berks</institution>
      <description>The Undergraduate Journal of Service Learning and Community-Based Research adds to the increasing number of scholarly journals that invite undergraduates to pursue their own intellectual projects. We seek undergraduate contributions to the burgeoning academic conversation on service learning and community-based research. The Undergraduate Journal of Service Learning and Community-Based Research is open to undergraduate students in the U.S. and across the globe in all subject areas. All submissions will undergo a rigorous review process.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>New Errands: The Undergraduate Journal of American Studies</title>
      <URL>https://journals.psu.edu/ne/</URL>
      <institution>Penn State University - Harrisburg</institution>
      <description>Seeking to develop the next generation of Americanists, New Errands’ mission is to provide a venue for the publication of important original scholarship by emerging young scholars and to provide a teaching resource for instructors of American Studies looking for exemplary work to use in the classroom. New Errands is jointly published by the Eastern American Studies Association and the American Studies Program at Penn State Harrisburg.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Dialectics: Undergraduate Journal of Leadership, Politics, and Society</title>
      <URL>http://sites.psu.edu/dialectics/</URL>
      <institution>Pennsylvania State University </institution>
      <description>The Dialectics is an electronic journal devoted to undergraduate scholarship and discourse. The journal welcomes high-quality essays on issues of public importance.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Pi Sigma Alpha Undergraduate Journal of Politics</title>
      <URL>http://www.psajournal.org/</URL>
      <institution>Pi Sigma Alpha</institution>
      <description>The Pi Sigma Alpha Undergraduate Journal of Politics (ISSN: 1556-2034) was founded in the spring of 2001 by the Delta Omega Chapter of Pi Sigma Alpha at Purdue University, under the name The American Undergraduate Journal of Politics and Government. With the sponsorship of Pi Sigma Alpha, the National Political Science Honor Society, the name of the Journal was changed to The Pi Sigma Alpha Undergraduate Journal of Politics beginning with the Fall 2004 issue. From July 2007 until July 2010 the Journal was based at the Zeta Upsilon Chapter at Union College, and in August 2010 moved to the Eta Rho Chapter at the College of William &amp; Mary. In August 2013, the Nu Omega Chapter at Oakland University began hosting the Journal for a three year term!</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Anthos</title>
      <URL>http://pdxscholar.library.pdx.edu/anthos/</URL>
      <institution>Portland State University</institution>
      <description>Founded in 1990, Anthós is a multidisciplinary academic journal published by the Honors College of Portland State University. Anthós publishes the work of Portland State University students, juried by Honors College student editors in a double-blind review process.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>PURSUE</title>
      <URL>http://www.pvamu.edu/pursue/</URL>
      <institution>Prairie View A &amp; M University</institution>
      <description>As a scholarly journal, “PURSUE” seeks to provide undergraduates with an avenue to publish their original research articles. The original research articles included in this journal are peer-reviewed and selected by the journal’s Editorial Board. The journal is housed at Prairie View A&amp;M University, an Historically Black University, and is available to all young scientists conducting research. This journal also serves as a means for faculty to extend knowledge beyond the classroom and encourage other students to conduct quality research. All undergraduate research is produced in conjunction with a faculty mentor and is peer reviewed. The journal is open to all undergraduates.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Princeton Innovation</title>
      <URL>http://www.princetoninnovation.org</URL>
      <institution>Princeton University</institution>
      <description>Princeton Innovation is an undergraduate science organization dedicated to making science more accessible to all students at Princeton. We publish articles highlighting science news on campus as well as groundbreaking research across the world. In addition to our articles, we host many events on campus to raise the level of science engagement and knowledge.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Sociology between the Gaps (SBG): Forgotten and Neglected Topics</title>
      <URL>https://digitalcommons.providence.edu/sbg/</URL>
      <institution>Providence College</institution>
      <description>Sociology between the Gaps (SBG) publishes high-quality, original articles including research notes, critical essays, and review papers which fall into subfields in sociological work that may be viewed by some as outside mainstream sociological topics; hence the full journal title: Sociology between the Gaps: Forgotten and Neglected Topics. The journal also aims to reflect the intersections of social class, race, gender, age, and cross-disciplinary views by encouraging sociologists and professionals in related fields to submit work on topics that cross disciplinary boundaries and/or areas of specialization but effectively link disciplines to provide a multi-disciplinary perspective on the topics addressed. The Editorial Board encourages original, unpublished papers in the field of sociology written by undergraduate or graduate students to be submitted to SBG. High-quality, well-written student papers may be submitted either by the author(s) of the paper or by the faculty advisor/mentor of students who are currently enrolled in the pursuit of an undergraduate or graduate degree. The submitted work should be reviewed by the student's faculty mentor for whom the paper was written before it is sent to the Editor-in-Chief of SBG. Student submitters are NOT required to be sociology majors.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Purdue Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://docs.lib.purdue.edu/jpur/</URL>
      <institution>Purdue University </institution>
      <description>The Journal of Purdue Undergraduate Research publishes outstanding research papers written by Purdue undergraduates from all academic disciplines who have completed a faculty-mentored research projects.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The International Journal for Undergraduate Research - Science, Engineering &amp; Technology (IJUR-SET)</title>
      <URL>http://www.qscience.com/page/ijur-set/ji_ijur-set</URL>
      <institution>Qatar Foundation</institution>
      <description>The International Journal for Undergraduate Research - Science, Engineering &amp; Technology (IJUR-SET) is a peer-reviewed journal for undergraduate work of the highest caliber. Its goals are to add to the body of knowledge in science and technology fields and to showcase the outstanding research activities of undergraduates. It provides a forum for students to publicly share their research, offering opportunities for exposing their work to potential graduate programs and employers. The journal accepts individual and collaborative research reports, formally written by the undergraduate students. Faculty-mentored research papers will also be considered. Any undergraduate student may submit work to this journal, and to be eligible for publication, the research must be faculty mentored. Submissions are accepted at any time. The Journal publishes twice a year (February and September).</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>QUEST Website</title>
      <URL>https://www.quest-journal.org/contact</URL>
      <institution>Queens University of Charlotte</institution>
      <description>QUEST (or Queens University of Charlotte Explorations in Science and Technology) Journal is a by-students, for students, undergraduate science research journal. Students at Queens University of Charlotte act as the editorial board, accept submissions, solicit peer reviewers from outside the institution, and publish the journal online. We accept all forms of science so long as the authors are willing to publish in the generalized format of introduction, methods, results, discussion. Data must be collected in a robust, scientific, way.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Corrupted Files</title>
      <URL>http://www.corruptedfiles.org.uk/</URL>
      <institution>Ravensbourne, UK</institution>
      <description>Corrupted Files is a non-hierarchical journal of research by students at all levels of study (Levels 4-7) and staff at Ravensbourne, as well as that of external contributors. The journal was initiated by Contextual Studies at Ravensbourne, with Dr Sara Andersdotter as its Editor. Corrupted Files is thematic, open access, and published annually in both online and hardcopy formats. Its aim is to serve as a platform through which undergraduate work is shared as research, sitting alongside the research of more experienced academics and practitioners. The journal thus plays a crucial part in a strategic drive towards the support and dissemination of undergraduate research, and the creation of a more inclusive research culture.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Catalyst: Rice Undergraduate Science &amp; Engineering Review</title>
      <URL>http://catalyst.rice.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Rice University</institution>
      <description>Catalyst is a student-run journal that showcases and highlights student research and views about science. Catalyst provides an avenue for students to share their thoughts and ideas about scientific innovations in the form of articles that are published annually.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Rice Historical Review</title>
      <URL>http://www.ricehistoricalreview.org/</URL>
      <institution>Rice University</institution>
      <description>The Rice Historical Review is a student-run, open access journal published online and in print. It features outstanding historically focused papers written by Rice undergraduates.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Rollins Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://scholarship.rollins.edu/rurj/</URL>
      <institution>Rollins University </institution>
      <description>The Rollins Undergraduate Research Journal is an online, peer-reviewed journal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Rose-Hulman Undergraduate Mathematics Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.rose-hulman.edu/mathjournal/</URL>
      <institution>Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology</institution>
      <description>The Rose-Hulman Undergraduate Mathematics Journal is devoted entirely to papers written by undergraduates on topics related to mathematics. Although the authors need not be undergraduates at the time of submission or publication, the work must have been completed before graduation.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Roshangar: Roshan Undergraduate Persian Studies Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.roshangarumd.com/</URL>
      <institution>Roshan Institute for Persian Studies, School of
                                                Languages, Literatures, and Cultures, University of
                                                Maryland, College Park</institution>
      <description>The Roshan Undergraduate Persian Studies Journal is a project initiated by the Roshan Undergraduate Ambassadors as part of University of Maryland’s Persian Studies program.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Laridae - Salisbury University Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www.salisbury.edu/administration/academic-affairs/graduate-studies-and-research/ourca/index.aspx</URL>
      <institution>Salisbury University</institution>
      <description>Laridae is an interdisciplinary, undergraduate research journal, which showcases academic and creative works from Salisbury University’s undergraduate student body. The journal is aimed at providing aspiring scholars with a platform to showcase their work in a low-stakes environment, which encourages diversity of thought and risk-taking. Salisbury University works to foster an academic environment where students are empowered to develop critical thinking and chase ideas from inception to resolution. Laridae seeks to facilitate and further augment SU's academic environment by offering a high-quality forum for the pursuit of knowledge.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Measure: A Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://journals.tdl.org/measure/index.php/measure/index</URL>
      <institution>Sam Houston State University</institution>
      <description>The Measure: A Journal of Undergraduate Research is a refereed journal dedicated to publishing undergraduate research from courses in the College of Humanities and Social Sciences at Sam Houston State University. Students enrolled in a CHSS course during the academic year are eligible to submit their work for publication consideration, whether or not they are majoring in one of the disciplines in the college. The Measure is guided by these central principles: undergraduate research is a vital component of higher education; students enhance their education when they engage in original research to make an intellectual contribution to the discipline; research shared with a broader audience enhances learning outcomes; and faculty members contribute to society when they involve undergraduates in research opportunities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Southern California International Review</title>
      <URL>http://www.scinternationalreview.org</URL>
      <institution>Southern California International Review</institution>
      <description>SCIR is a global undergraduate international studies journal published biannually and funded by the School of International Relations at the University of Southern California (USC). Article topics published in the journal range from economic and political issues to cultural and social themes. The journal seeks to foster and enhance discussion between theoretical and policy-oriented research regarding significant global issues.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Discovery: The SMSU Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://archives.smsu.edu/islandora/object/SMSUrepository%3A17433#page/1/mode/2up</URL>
      <institution>Southwest Minnesota State University</institution>
      <description>The journal features exceptional research and writing by SMSU undergraduates.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Student Research</title>
      <URL>http://www.stu.edu/jsr</URL>
      <institution>St. Thomas University</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Student Research (JSR) is a digital, international, multidisciplinary journal devoted to publishing quality, original, scholarly research articles on a variety of topics related to business, communication, education, law, science and technology, and other current research topics. The JSR provides a venue for students to publish current and significant research. The JSR accepts submissions of empirical and conceptual research that tests, extends, or builds theory and contributes to current research topics. The Journal of Student Research is published in the fall and spring of each academic year.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Intersect: The Stanford Journal of Science, Technology and Society</title>
      <URL>http://ojs.stanford.edu/ojs/index.php/intersect</URL>
      <institution>Stanford University</institution>
      <description>Intersect is an international Science, Technology, and Society research journal run by undergraduate students at Stanford University and supported by the Program in STS. It welcomes undergraduate, graduate, and PhD submissions at the intersection of history, culture, sociology, art, literature, business, law, and design with science and technology. The journal's submissions are not exclusive to Stanford affiliates and generally span several continents.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Word: The Stanford Journal of Student Hiphop Research</title>
      <URL>https://theword.su.domains/</URL>
      <institution>Stanford University</institution>
      <description>Launched in Fall 2019, The Word is a student hiphop research journal that aims to embody the founding spirit and purpose of hiphop: providing a mode of creative expression and voice to marginalized communities, inspiring activism, and making a way outta no way.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Stanford Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://surj.stanford.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Stanford University </institution>
      <description>The Stanford Undergraduate Research Journal (SURJ) is an annual peer-reviewed publication of research articles written primarily by Stanford undergraduates, but also by well-qualified students at other institutions, from all academic fields.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Explorations</title>
      <URL>http://explorations.tamu.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Texas A&amp;M University-College Station</institution>
      <description>Explorations is a student-run journal guided by faculty and administrators that selects and publishes student-authored articles of general interest in any area. Articles are submitted in a two-stage process: first, proposals for articles are reviewed by faculty-student teams; second, the resulting full-length articles undergo a second round of peer review. Acceptance to the journal is competitive—only 10-20 percent of submitted proposals are accepted. Recently published articles have been from a wide range of academic fields: music, creative poetry, forensics, cancer biology, astrophysics, nanomedicine, computer algorithms, business, geosciences, sociology, aerospace engineering, and cultural anthropology.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>URJe - The Undergraduate Research Journal of AUC</title>
      <URL>https://urje.aucegypt.edu/</URL>
      <institution>The American University in Cairo</institution>
      <description>The American University in Cairo's Undergraduate Research Journal (URJe) is an open access multi-disciplinary, refereed annual publication for undergraduate research and creative works. It is managed and published jointly by the Office for Undergraduate Research and the Main Library at the American University in Cairo.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Inventio</title>
      <URL>http://inventio.cua.edu/</URL>
      <institution>The Catholic University of America</institution>
      <description>Inventio is the multidisciplinary undergraduate research journal of The Catholic University of America. Established in 2015, it aims to identify and disseminate original undergraduate research that best represents the university’s commitment to the academic and Catholic traditions that inform its mission to “discover and impart the truth.” The journal accepts submissions of research in theology, philosophy, the humanities, and the social sciences written by current students or within two years of their graduation.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The North Star Reports: Global Citizenship and Digital Literacy</title>
      <URL>http://northstarreports.org/write-for-us/</URL>
      <institution>The North Star Reports</institution>
      <description>College and high school students wishing to submit brief articles should first visit this page, http://northstarreports.org/write-for-us/. We accept articles 2 pages or shorter concerning all aspects pertaining to global and historical connections.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>SIAM Undergraduate Research Online (SIURO)</title>
      <URL>http://www.siam.org/students/siuro/</URL>
      <institution>The Society For Industrial and Applied
                                                Mathematics (SIAM)</institution>
      <description>SIURO is devoted to undergraduate research in applied and computational mathematics. The wide range of applied topics published include analysis, discrete mathematics, statistics, operations research, optimization, dynamical systems, modeling, computation, and more.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Popular Archaeology</title>
      <URL>http://popular-archaeology.com/page/the-student-scholar-program</URL>
      <institution>The Student Scholar Program</institution>
      <description>The Student Scholar Program provides a means for college students or recent graduates to publish academic papers before a global audience. These are papers that were written by the students to fulfill class and graduation requirements of their respective academic institutions. Papers submitted will be evaluated and those selected will be published as articles in the Anthropology Journal of the online magazine, Popular Archaeology. Some will be published as specially featured papers, prominently visible on the home page of the magazine.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Undergraduate Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.undergraduateawards.com/prizedetails/journal/</URL>
      <institution>The Undergraduate Awards</institution>
      <description>Cited as the ultimate champion for high-potential undergraduates, The Undergraduate Awards is the world’s largest academic awards programme. It is uniquely pan-discipline, identifying leading creative thinkers through their undergraduate coursework. The Undergraduate Awards provides top performing students with the support, network and opportunities they require to raise their profiles and further their career paths, as well as coming to Dublin for an all-expenses-paid trip to receive their medal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Perpetua: The UAH Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://www.uah.edu/perpetua</URL>
      <institution>The University of Alabama in Huntsville</institution>
      <description>Perpetua is a journal that highlights the research performed at UAH by publishing peer-reviewed articles submitted by undergraduates.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Chicago Journal of Foreign Policy</title>
      <URL>https://thecjfp.com/</URL>
      <institution>The University of Chicago</institution>
      <description>The Chicago Journal of Foreign Policy (CJFP) is a journal published by undergraduates at The University of Chicago that aims to provide a forum for problem-solving and analysis around international affairs. The journal, founded in 2012, features a collection of articles that reflect on historical, economic, political, and cultural developments within nations other than the United States, or explores relationships between the United States and the world. Each edition covers topics from regions around the world, and engages in ongoing discussions held on the international stage. Our biannual edition, published in the early winter and late spring, serves as a complement to our regularly updated online publication, featuring articles, op-eds, and blog posts produced and edited by our staff and by other students at our university. CJFP is a registered student organization (RSO) of UChicago.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Chicago Journal of Foreign Policy</title>
      <URL>https://thecjfp.com</URL>
      <institution>The University of Chicago</institution>
      <description>Founded in 2012, the Chicago Journal of Foreign Policy (CJFP) is a journal published by undergraduates at the University of Chicago that aims to provide a forum for problem-solving and analysis around international affairs.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Midway Review</title>
      <URL>http://midwayreview.uchicago.edu</URL>
      <institution>The University of Chicago</institution>
      <description>The Midway Review is a journal of essays published in print and online three times a year at the University of Chicago. Founded in 2005 as a forum for political, cultural, and literary exchange across political and disciplinary boundaries, the Review seeks to publish readable, polished essays on all topics that would engage a general intellectual audience. We also publish book, film, music, and television reviews, as well as interviews. We do not publish academic papers unless they have been revised into essays—the first-person form of something you might read in Harper's or The New Yorker. We accept work from students, alumni, and faculty at all colleges and universities. We consider submissions each year in October, January, and April.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal for Undergraduate Research Opportunities</title>
      <URL>http://curo.uga.edu/juro</URL>
      <institution>The University of Georgia</institution>
      <description>The Journal for Undergraduate Research Opportunities at the University of Georgia is an undergraduate research journal for humanities, social sciences, policy, and arts. The journal is dedicated to promoting research as a part of the undergraduate experience by providing undergraduates an opportunity to publish their work.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Contemporary</title>
      <URL>https://thecontemporarygroup.com/</URL>
      <institution>Trinity University </institution>
      <description>The Contemporary is a student-run startup publication based at Trinity University that empowers collegiate journalists nationwide to report on critical issues in their communities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>TuftScope</title>
      <URL>http://www.tuftscope.squarespace.com</URL>
      <institution>Tufts University</institution>
      <description>Since 2001, TuftScope: The Interdisciplinary Journal of Health, Ethics, &amp; Policy has provided an academic forum for discussion of pertinent health care and biosocial issues in today's world. The journal addresses different aspects of health care, bioethics, public health, policy, and active citizenship. It is operated and edited by undergraduate students of Tufts University and is advised by an Editorial Board composed of Tufts undergraduates and faculty. New issues are released biannually in print and online versions.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Journal of Psychology at Berkeley</title>
      <URL>http://ujpb.org</URL>
      <institution>UC Berkeley</institution>
      <description>The Undergraduate Journal of Psychology at Berkeley is an annual publication that allows undergraduate students who have completed scientific studies in psychology and psychology-related fields to publish their findings to the larger academic community, promoting further and more excellent undergraduate research. UJPB accepts and reviews submissions from all psychology-related fields, including psychology, neuroscience, cognitive science, and linguistics, as long as the papers are the original work of undergraduate students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UC Riverside Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://ssp.ucr.edu/journal/</URL>
      <institution>UC Riverside</institution>
      <description>The University of California Riverside Undergraduate Research Journal provides a student-edited multi-disciplinary journal that features the very best faculty-mentored undergraduate research and scholarship accomplished on our campus. This peer review process is managed by the Student Editorial Board (SEB) with guidance from the Faculty Advisory Board (FAB), and logistic support from Undergraduate Education’s Educational Initiatives. The Journal is sponsored by the Vice Provost for Undergraduate Education.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Aleph: UCLA Undergraduate Research Journal for Humanities and Social Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://aleph.humanities.ucla.edu/</URL>
      <institution>UCLA</institution>
      <description>Aleph is UCLA’s only official journal publishing undergraduate research in the humanities, social sciences, and behavioral sciences. Run by undergraduates who review submissions continuously throughout the year, Aleph publishes select submissions in a quarterly online journal and an annual “best of” print journal, with the support of our sponsor, the UCLA Undergraduate Research Center.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Journal of Psychology at UCLA</title>
      <URL>https://urjp.psych.ucla.edu/</URL>
      <institution>UCLA</institution>
      <description/>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UNC JOURney</title>
      <URL>https://uncjourney.unc.edu/</URL>
      <institution>UNC Chapel Hill</institution>
      <description>This annual journal is dedicated to the publication of outstanding faculty-mentored research conducted by current undergraduate students at UNC-Chapel Hill. Research in the disciplines of natural sciences, social sciences, and humanities is published.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>IJSRA Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.ijsra.org/</URL>
      <institution>Unaffiliated</institution>
      <description>Peer-reviewed, free and open-access international forum for the exchange of excellent student scholarship in archaeology. Find us on Facebook! Submit your manuscripts to ijsra.editor@gmail.com Executive Editor: Gonzalo Linares, BA Archaeology &amp; Anthropology, University of Oxford (UK)</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>JOSHUA: Journal of Science and Health at the University of Alabama</title>
      <URL>https://undergraduateresearch.as.ua.edu/presenting-your-work/joshua/</URL>
      <institution>University of Alabama</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Science and Health at the University of Alabama (JOSHUA) is an undergraduate research journal relating to science and health.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Inquiro</title>
      <URL>http://www.uab.edu/undergraduateresearch/</URL>
      <institution>University of Alabama at Birmingham</institution>
      <description>Inquiro is UAB's official journal of undergraduate research. The Journal operates by a blind, peer review process conducted by UAB faculty, researchers, and distinguished undergraduate students and maintains the highest standards of scholastic integrity.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Spectrum</title>
      <URL>http://www.spectrumjournal.ca</URL>
      <institution>University of Alberta</institution>
      <description>Spectrum is a student-run, interdisciplinary journal that strives to publish diverse and engaging research completed by undergraduate students within and across the areas of health sciences, natural sciences and engineering, social sciences, arts and humanities. English-language submissions are welcome from undergraduate students at any postsecondary institution. Spectrum is managed by the Undergraduate Research Initiative at the University of Alberta (www.uri.ualberta.ca)</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>DISCOVERY</title>
      <URL>https://scholarworks.uark.edu/discoverymag/</URL>
      <institution>University of Arkansas</institution>
      <description>Discovery is the undergraduate student research journal at the Dale Bumpers College of Agricultural, Food and Life Sciences.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Inquiry: The University of Arkansas Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://inquiry.uark.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of Arkansas</institution>
      <description>The Inquiry Journal accepts research works as well as creative works for publication. Research includes any quantitative or qualitative original research that a student has conducted during their academic studies. Creative works include any theoretical works, policy analyses, art projects or displays, among others.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Canadian Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://cjur.ca/</URL>
      <institution>University of British Columbia</institution>
      <description>The Canadian Journal of Undergraduate Research (CJUR) is a biannual publication that highlights work being done by undergraduates in all areas of academic research. CJUR publishes a variety of article types, including primary research, reviews, commentaries, and critiques. All submissions are reviewed by experienced graduate students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>JEMI+</title>
      <URL>http://jemi.microbiology.ubc.ca/</URL>
      <institution>University of British Columbia</institution>
      <description>Since 2001, the Journal of Experimental Microbiology &amp; Immunology (JEMI) has published original research conducted by undergraduates at the University of British Columbia. In 2015, JEMI was expanded to JEMI+, and international, peer-reviewed journal dedicated to enhancing undergraduate learning and experiences by providing thorough and constructive reviews from experts in the fields of microbiology and immunology.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Berkeley Scientific Journal</title>
      <URL>http://bsj.berkeley.edu/?page_id=546</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Berkeley</institution>
      <description>Started in 1996, Berkeley Scientific Journal (BSJ) is the official and oldest undergraduate science journal of the University of California, Berkeley. Each semester, BSJ publishes feature articles; interviews with faculty; and peer-reviewed, independent research articles spanning diverse scientific disciplines.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Berkeley Undergraduate Journal</title>
      <URL>http://learning.berkeley.edu/buj/</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Berkeley</institution>
      <description>Established in 1987, the Berkeley Undergraduate Journal is a student-run journal that publishes exceptional undergraduate academic papers from the social sciences and humanities at UC Berkeley.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UC Berkeley Comparative Literature Undergraduate Journal</title>
      <URL>https://ucbcluj.org/</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Berkeley</institution>
      <description>CLUJ provides undergraduate students around the world the opportunity to publish and share their research with an international audience. The Journal was founded by a comparative literature undergraduate student in 2011 and has since been recognized as a premier undergraduate journal featuring top peer-reviewed, undergraduate research in comparative literature. We invite abstracts from those working in, around, or critically engaging with topics in literature from a comparative nature, broadly construed. Possible topics include interdisciplinary research across disciplines within the arts and sciences (e.g., literature and philosophy, literature and history, literature and science, and literature and new media); research engaging with literary theory and ‘schools of criticism’ (e.g., gender studies and queer theory, postmodernism, cultural studies, Frankfurt School and critical theory, structuralism and semiotics, psychoanalysis, animal studies, and posthumanism); and articles comparing at least two authors or texts, print, and/or media.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Berkeley Economic Review</title>
      <URL>https://www.ocf.berkeley.edu/~uea/</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Berkeley</institution>
      <description>The Undergraduate Berkeley Economic Review is the University of California at Berkeley’s premier undergraduate, peer-reviewed, academic economics journal. Established by the Undergraduate Economics Association at Berkeley, we are a 100% student-run and student-produced nonprofit publication. We publish undergraduate research papers and honors theses in the field of economics. We also accept academic term papers and class essays, as well as op-eds on our world’s current political economy. In addition, we publish professor interviews and faculty research abstracts. All students currently enrolled in an accredited four-year college or university are welcome to submit content for review via email: berkeleyeconreview@gmail.com</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Clio's Scroll, The Berkeley Undergraduate History Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www.ocf.berkeley.edu/~clios/</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Berkeley, Department
                                                of History</institution>
      <description>Clio’s Scroll, the Berkeley Undergraduate History Journal, is published twice yearly by students of the Department of History at the University of California, Berkeley. The journal aims to provide undergraduates with the opportunity to publish historical works, develop the editing and writing skills of contributors and board members, and train them in the editorial process of an academic journal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Falsafa: Undergraduate Journal of Philosophy</title>
      <URL>https://falsafaorg.com/</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Irvine</institution>
      <description>Falsafa aims to highlight philosophical ideas and research in marginalized/underrepresented subdisciplines and aims to encourage work by undergraduates within the same. Falsafa welcomes submissions on topics pertaining to all areas of philosophy and encourages undergraduates from all universities, majors, and backgrounds to submit creative works.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The UCI Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.urop.uci.edu/journal.html</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Irvine</institution>
      <description>The UCI Undergraduate Research Journal, produced by UROP, is a compilation of outstanding papers submitted by UCI undergraduate students from all disciplines who have completed faculty-mentored research projects or creative activities. It provides a forum for UCI’s best undergraduate researchers to showcase their work while enlightening students, the UCI community, high schools, community colleges, funding agencies, and corporations about the strength of UCI’s undergraduate research community.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UCLA Undergraduate Science Journal</title>
      <URL>https://uclausj.weebly.com/</URL>
      <institution>University of California, Los Angeles</institution>
      <description>The UCLA Undergraduate Science Journal (USJ) is a student-run academic journal showcasing original research and review articles submitted by undergraduate authors.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Saltman Quarterly</title>
      <URL>https://sqonline.ucsd.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of California, San Diego
                                                (UCSD)</institution>
      <description>Saltman Quarterly is an undergraduate research journal and science communication program hosted by UCSD's Division of Biology. The student-run organization gives undergraduates an opportunity to get their original biology research and review papers published in a professional journal. The organization also allows undergraduates to get involved in local science literacy initiatives and improve their own science communication.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UCF Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www.urj.ucf.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of Central Florida</institution>
      <description>The University of Central Florida Undergraduate Research Journal is a peer-reviewed undergraduate journal published online. Its mission is to showcase articles of exemplary works from a wide range of student scholarship in all fields.The journal seeks outstanding research submitted by undergraduate UCF students who have been involved in faculty-mentored research projects and activities related to scholarship.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Missouri Journal of Mathematical Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://www.ucmo.edu/math-cs/journal/</URL>
      <institution>University of Central Missouri</institution>
      <description>The Missouri Journal of Mathematical Sciences (MJMS) publishes well-motivated original research articles as well as expository and survey articles of exceptional quality in mathematical sciences.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>1890: A Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://newplainsreview.com/1890-uco/</URL>
      <institution>University of Central Oklahoma</institution>
      <description>1890: A Journal of Undergraduate Research invites undergraduate students from all universities to submit their work—from any discipline—to be considered for publication in our undergraduate research journal. The journal is interdisciplinary, meaning that research, scholarly articles, creative writing, artwork, and photography will all be placed under consideration. For more information, please see our call for submissions at our website.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Triple Helix at the University of Chicago</title>
      <URL>http://thetriplehelix.uchicago.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of Chicago</institution>
      <description>Scientia is the interdisciplinary scientific research journal at the University of Chicago published by the Triple Helix, Inc. The Triple Helix is the world's largest completely student-run organization, with more that 25 chapters worldwide that focus on evaluating the impact of modern and historic advances in science. Scientia in particular seeks to publish rigorously selected and edited undergraduate research articles and abstracts accessible to a wide audience. Having expanded beyond our campus to the Midwest region, we seek to reach a national community of undergraduate scholars.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Queen City Writers</title>
      <URL>http://qc-writers.com/</URL>
      <institution>University of Cincinnati</institution>
      <description>We seek thought-provoking pieces from any disciplinary perspective that explore questions and problems related to writing, rhetoric, reading, literacy broadly conceived, popular culture and media, community discourses, and multimodal and digital composing. We expect that the work will be informed by critical conversations relevant to the topic–that is, composers should incorporate timely, pertinent research to support claims. In addition, we welcome projects that experiment with form, voice, style, and delivery.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://ufdc.ufl.edu/jur</URL>
      <institution>University of Florida</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Undergraduate Research publishes the outstanding scholarship of undergraduates at the University of Florida and showcases the work of students in the University Scholars Program.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Classic Journal at University of Georgia</title>
      <URL>http://theclassicjournal.uga.edu/index.php/about/</URL>
      <institution>University of Georgia</institution>
      <description>The Classic Journal promotes the extraordinary achievements in writing and research by undergraduates in the Writing Intensive Program (WIP) at the University of Georgia. The Classic Journal is a cross-disciplinary publication, fostering a community of diverse writers throughout the arts, humanities, and sciences.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Peer Review: The Undergraduate Research Journal of the Ethnography of the University Initiative</title>
      <URL>https://ugresearchjournals.illinois.edu/index.php/preui/index</URL>
      <institution>University of Illinois at
                                                Urbana-Champaign</institution>
      <description>Peer Review is an open-access, digital journal that publishes research-based articles and multimedia projects by current and recent undergraduates who participate in EUI-affiliated courses or students in non-EUI-related courses or programs of study whose research engages the university in a meaningful way.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Re:Search, The Undergraduate Literary Criticism Journal at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign</title>
      <URL>https://ugresearchjournals.illinois.edu/index.php/ujlc/index</URL>
      <institution>University of Illinois at
                                                Urbana-Champaign</institution>
      <description>Re:Search: The Undergraduate Literary Criticism Journal at UIUC is an undergraduate produced, peer-reviewed online journal designed to annually publish works exclusively by undergraduate students. It seeks to create a venue for undergraduate students to showcase and publish literary criticism within a greater academic discourse while nurturing a collaborative community between faculty, administration, and undergraduate students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Watcher Junior: The Undergraduate Journal of Whedon Studies</title>
      <URL>http://www.whedonstudies.tv/watcher-junior-the-undergraduate-journal-of-whedon-studies.html</URL>
      <institution>University of Maine at Farmington</institution>
      <description>As colleges and universities include the work of Joss Whedon in courses on media studies, history, psychology, religion, race and gender studies, cultural studies and more students continue to produce Whedon scholarship at the undergraduate level. Slayage provides a forum for publishing graduate and professional scholarship. In its tenth year of publication Watcher Junior, a peer-reviewed online journal, remains committed to doing the same for undergraduate work in Whedon studies.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Catalyst Undergraduate Bioengineering Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.bioe.umd.edu/sites/default/files/documents/thecatalyst-issue1.pdf</URL>
      <institution>University of Maryland</institution>
      <description>The Catalyst is the University of Maryland's undergraduate bioengineering research journal. We are looking to publish a variety of bioengineering and biotechnology related research in issues published once per semester! Research abstracts can be written based on faculty-run lab research, internship/co-op work, or Gemstone/ Honors program research. If you have any questions, please feel free to email us at thecatalystumd@gmail.com. Please get approval from your PI to submit your research to this on-campus publication. Also, do not forget to like us on Facebook at www.Facebook.com/CatalystUMD and feel free to pass this message on to anyone that you think might be interested.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Scientific Terrapin</title>
      <URL>http://scientificterrapin.umd.edu</URL>
      <institution>University of Maryland, College Park</institution>
      <description>Scientific Terrapin, the University of Maryland's undergraduate research journal, publishes original student research in applied sciences, natural sciences, and social sciences.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Michigan Journal of Business</title>
      <URL>http://michiganjb.org/</URL>
      <institution>University of Michigan</institution>
      <description>The Michigan Journal of Business is a peer-reviewed academic journal published biannually by undergraduates at the Stephen M. Ross School of Business at the University of Michigan. The journal seeks to publish distinguished theses, empirical research, case studies, and theories relating to the areas of Accounting, Economics, Finance, Marketing, Management, Operations Management, Information Systems, Business Law, Corporate Ethics, and Public Policy.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Michigan Journal of Political Science</title>
      <URL>https://mjps.polisci.lsa.umich.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of Michigan</institution>
      <description/>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>University of Michigan Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://umurj.org/</URL>
      <institution>University of Michigan</institution>
      <description>Student-run, nontechnical research journal. Our mission is to build connections among undergraduate, graduate students, and the public, as well as among the different academic disciplines, through the publication of nontechnical articles in all fields of research.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Epistemai: An Undergraduate Journal of Philosophy</title>
      <URL>https://cla.umn.edu/philosophy/undergraduate/real-world-experience/philosophy-undergraduate-journal</URL>
      <institution>University of Minnesota-Twin Cities</institution>
      <description>Epistemai is an undergraduate philosophy journal with a focus on short, original, philosophical work done by undergraduates from universities across the country.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UMURJ Website</title>
      <URL>http://umurjournal.wix.com/umurj</URL>
      <institution>University of Mississippi</institution>
      <description>A student run, peer reviewed journal for students at the University of Mississippi publishing work in engineering, natural sciences, social sciences, and the humanities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Lucerna</title>
      <URL>https://honors.umkc.edu/get-involved/lucerna/</URL>
      <institution>University of Missouri-Kansas City</institution>
      <description>Lucerna is a peer-reviewed, interdisciplinary journal and UMKC's only undergraduate research journal, publishing articles by students in the social sciences, sciences, and humanities. Established in 2005 by the UMKC Honors Program, Lucerna cultivates and showcases high-caliber scholarship from the entire UMKC undergraduate community.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>RURALS: Review of Undergraduate Research in Agricultural and Life Sciences</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.unl.edu/rurals/</URL>
      <institution>University of Nebraska-Lincoln</institution>
      <description>A faculty-refereed journal devoted to the publication of high quality research by undergraduates worldwide in all research problem areas including, but not limited to, those described in the USDA, CSREES Manual of Classification of Agricultural and Forestry Research. Maintained at the Institute of Agriculture and Natural Resources at the University of Nebraska, Lincoln. Articles by graduate students will be considered if the work has been completed as undergraduates. Articles are instantly issued upon acceptanc</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Inquiry Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.unh.edu/inquiryjournal/</URL>
      <institution>University of New Hampshire</institution>
      <description>Inquiry journal is the online, multi-disciplinary undergraduate research journal of the University of New Hampshire. It is published annually in April.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Xchanges</title>
      <URL>http://www.xchanges.org/</URL>
      <institution>University of New Mexico</institution>
      <description>Xchanges is an interdisciplinary Technical Communication, Writing/Rhetoric, and Writing Across the Curriculum journal, which publishes two issues annually from its home in the English Department at the University of New Mexico. Our Fall issue each year features undergraduate research. Our Spring issue features graduate-student research. In each undergraduate issue, we publish theses and research projects of upper-level undergraduate students. Our graduate-student issues feature MA- and Ph.D.-level original research from emerging professionals in our focal fields. We receive submissions from students from a wide array of institutions across the country and abroad. Our faculty review board, comprised of TC, Comp/Rhet, and WAC faculty from throughout the U.S., reviews these submissions on a “blind” basis. We welcome undergraduate and graduate students in these disciplines to submit their work to Xchanges, either as traditional articles or as multimodal “webtexts.” Please see our "Submission Information" tab for more information.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Explorations</title>
      <URL>http://uncw.edu/csurf/Explorations/explorations.html</URL>
      <institution>University of North Carolina Wilmington</institution>
      <description>Explorations is a refereed journal that features original research and creative work by students at any 2- or 4- year public or private college or university across the state of North Carolina. Explorations is the companion journal for the annual State of North Carolina Undergraduate Research and Creativity Symposium (SCNURCS) and publishes student-authored articles of general interest in any area, as well as creative work in a variety of media. Article submission is June 1 of each year, and submissions are reviewed by a faculty board of reviewers across the state.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>PANDION: The Osprey Journal of Research and Ideas</title>
      <URL>https://digitalcommons.unf.edu/pandion_unf/</URL>
      <institution>University of North Florida</institution>
      <description>PANDION: The Osprey Journal of Research and Ideas is an online and print journal featuring the results of faculty-mentored and faculty-endorsed student research from all colleges and majors at the University of North Florida.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Papers &amp; Publications: Interdisciplinary Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.northgeorgia.edu/papersandpubs/</URL>
      <institution>University of North Georgia</institution>
      <description>Papers &amp; Publications is an open-access, peer-reviewed, interdisciplinary journal of undergraduate research and creative works published and supported by the Center for Undergraduate Research and Creative Activities (CURCA) at the University of North Georgia. The journal promotes student learning by disseminating undergraduate research and creative works that make an intellectual or creative contribution to the discipline or to applied practice.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Eagle Feather</title>
      <URL>http://eaglefeather.honors.unt.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of North Texas</institution>
      <description>The Eagle Feather is an interdisciplinary undergraduate research journal for students at the University of North Texas.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>OUR Journal - Oregon Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://ourj.uoregon.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of Oregon</institution>
      <description>The Oregon Undergraduate Research Journal (OUR Journal) is an open access undergraduate research journal at the University of Oregon. It showcases some of the best research and publications by UO undergraduate students.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Fenjan: The Middle East Journal</title>
      <URL>https://www.fenjanupenn.com/</URL>
      <institution>University of Pennsylvania</institution>
      <description>Fenjan is the University of Pennsylvania’s premier journal on the Middle East. Through nonpartisan, quarterly issues, Fenjan is dedicated to increasing empathy for and understanding of the Middle East among the Penn Community through written and visual work.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Penn Bioethics Journal</title>
      <URL>http://bioethicsjournal.com/index.html</URL>
      <institution>University of Pennsylvania</institution>
      <description>The Penn Bioethics Journal is the nation's premier peer-reviewed undergraduate bioethics journal. The journal was established in spring 2004 with the first issue published April 1, 2005, as part of the National Undergraduate Bioethics Conference hosted by Penn. The editorial board has included undergraduates from all four schools at the University of Pennsylvania with faculty advisors Jonathan D. Moreno, PhD, and Connie Ulrich, PhD, RN</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Penn Undergraduate Law Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.pulj.org</URL>
      <institution>University of Pennsylvania</institution>
      <description>A student-run research publication at the University of Pennsylvania, the Penn Undergraduate Law Journal seeks to foster scholarly discourse on topical and historical issues pertaining to law or the legal system. In this spirit, the journal's principal objective is to publish exceptional undergraduate works, drawn from an array of disciplinary perspectives, that evaluate and elucidate the intricacies, vagaries, and nuances of law as they relate to domestic and international affairs, business, academia, and society. PULJ aims to sustain and enrich a vibrant discussion about law at the undergraduate level because it recognizes that the student writers of today will be the leaders, lawyers, and scholars of tomorrow.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Forbes &amp; Fifth</title>
      <URL>http://forbes5.pitt.edu</URL>
      <institution>University of Pittsburgh</institution>
      <description>Forbes &amp; Fifth, a magazine published by Dietrich School undergraduates at the University of Pittsburgh, and sponsored by the Office of Undergraduate Research, Scholarship, and Creative Activity, unites works of research, creative writing, and scholarly articles under the banner of interdisciplinary collaboration. We seek articles of an interdisciplinary nature, both in form and content. We've featured research articles on Internet memes, Peruvian Terrorism, Mongolian folk rock, Great Britain's "Little Ice Age," as well as poetry, fiction, and creative nonfiction. We're also interested in visual art, translations, and reviews. Undergraduates at accredited institutions may submit inquiries or work to forbes5@pitt.edu.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Pittsburgh Undergraduate Review</title>
      <URL>http://www.pur.honorscollege.pitt.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of Pittsburgh</institution>
      <description>PUR is a multidisciplinary journal that accepts papers from around the world.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Digital America</title>
      <URL>http://www.digitalamerica.org</URL>
      <institution>University of Richmond</institution>
      <description>Digital America is a new, online journal that features student work on digitization, digital culture, and American life. We also feature process projects in courses that engage digital media and digital culture, and we feature ongoing commentary on topical, digital issues. We accept traditional papers as well as new media pieces, digital art, and short films.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://sa.rochester.edu/jur/index.html</URL>
      <institution>University of Rochester</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Undergraduate Research (JUR) is dedicated to providing the student body with intellectual perspectives from various academic disciplines. JUR serves as a forum for the presentation of original research, thereby encouraging the pursuit of significant scholarly endeavors.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>USURJ: Univ of Saskatchewan Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://www.usask.ca/usurj</URL>
      <institution>University of Saskatchewan</institution>
      <description>USURJ is an online, peer-reviewed scholarly journal featuring original work by University of Saskatchewan undergraduate students. Founded by University of Saskatchewan undergraduate students, the journal celebrates undergraduate contributions to research. USURJ publishes high-quality research and review articles written by undergraduates in all disciplines and professional colleges. All submissions are reviewed by established experts in a relevant field.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Caravel Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://caravel.sc.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of South Carolina</institution>
      <description>Caravel is a faculty-reviewed online undergraduate research journal, which chronicles students' creative research from all academic disciplines.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Oswald Review</title>
      <URL>https://scholarcommons.sc.edu/tor/</URL>
      <institution>University of South Carolina Aiken</institution>
      <description>An International Journal of Undergraduate Research and Criticism in the Discipline of English</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Undergraduate Journal of Mathematical Modeling: One + Two</title>
      <URL>http://scholarcommons.usf.edu/ujmm/</URL>
      <institution>University of South Florida (USF)</institution>
      <description>The open access Undergraduate Journal of Mathematical Modeling: One + Two is concerned with various applications of mathematics done by non-mathematics majors. In particular, its purpose is to disseminate selected applied mathematics projects of engineering and science students. A unique feature of this journal, as shown by its title, is that each student whose work is published has been advised by at least two different people: a subject area advisor (who typically, but not always, suggested the problem) and a mathematics advisor. Articles published by the open access "Undergraduate Journal of Mathematical Modeling: One + Two" are made available under a Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share Alike 3.0 license. http://scholarcommons.usf.edu/ujmm/editorialboard.html For more information please email: scholarcommons@usf.edu Rebel Cummings-Sauls</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Illumin</title>
      <URL>http://illumin.usc.edu/</URL>
      <institution>University of Southern California</institution>
      <description>Illumin is a student-run online magazine dedicated to the fields of science and technology, specifically engineering. Submissions to the magazine come from USC undergraduate engineers along with submissions from universities across the nation.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Modern Psychological Studies</title>
      <URL>https://new.utc.edu/arts-and-sciences/psychology/mps</URL>
      <institution>University of Tennessee at Chattanooga</institution>
      <description>Modern Psychological Studies (MPS) is a psychological journal devoted exclusively to publishing manuscripts by undergraduate students. We are continuously seeking quality manuscripts for publication and will consider manuscripts in any area of psychology. Although MPS primarily focuses on results from experimental research, there are also publication opportunities for theoretical papers, literature reviews, and book reviews.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Pursuit: The Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>http://trace.tennessee.edu/pursuit/</URL>
      <institution>University of Tennessee at Knoxville</institution>
      <description>Pursuit: The Journal of Undergraduate Research was founded in 2009. Pursuit is dedicated to publishing the scholarly work of undergraduates and is supported by the University of Tennessee Office of Research and the Chancellor’s Honors Program. The editors and review board are undergraduate students who consider and review submissions and work with select faculty and staff to publish Pursuit. All submissions must be double spaced and must be no longer than 30 pages (for Humanities and Social Sciences papers) or 15 pages (for Science and Engineering papers). Please use endnotes instead of footnotes. Submissions in the Sciences and Engineering fields should be written in the third person and should contain the following categories: abstract, introduction, methods, results, discussion/conclusions, references.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>UTPB Journal of Undergraduate Research</title>
      <URL>https://falconcommons.utpb.edu/utpb-jour/</URL>
      <institution>University of Texas Permian Basin</institution>
      <description>Welcome to the UTPB Journal of Undergraduate Research. With this journal we hope to share our students' research with the campus, region, nation, and wider global community. We publish not only abstracts of posters and presentations from our undergraduate research day, but also the actual posters, presentation slides, and full-length papers resulting from our students' research. We look forward to beginning a fruitful conversation based on research and scholarship in all disciplines done by the undergraduate students of the University of Texas Permian Basin.Aim: The aim of the UTPB Journal of Undergraduate Research is to share the best research occurring at the undergraduate level at the University of Texas of the Permian Basin with the global community. The UTPB Journal of Undergraduate Research is an interdisciplinary peer-reviewed journal covering undergraduate research in the physical and social sciences, arts, and humanities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Texas Undergraduate Research Journal (URJ)</title>
      <URL>http://texasurj.com/wp/</URL>
      <institution>University of Texas at Austin</institution>
      <description>The Texas Undergraduate Research Journal (URJ) is a work of multi-disciplinary research produced and edited by University of Texas at Austin undergraduate students. The journal is published every spring semester and is circulated across campus and other prestigious universities around the United States, including some Ivy League universities.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Developing Economist</title>
      <URL>http://www.developingeconomist.com/</URL>
      <institution>University of Texas at Austin</institution>
      <description>The Developing Economist is an Undergraduate Journal of Economics sponsored by the University of Texas Chapter of Omicron Delta Epsilon, The International Honor Society for Economics. Our mission is to publish outstanding research in the field of Economics, Mathematics, Public Policy, Finance, and International Relations, while fostering scientific learning within the UT community. By providing a venue for publication, The Developing Economist hopes to provide visibility to undergraduate research and establish a dialogue between students of economics at various levels.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Research and Scholarly Works</title>
      <URL>http://research.utsa.edu/UG_Journal/index.html</URL>
      <institution>University of Texas at San Antonio</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Undergraduate Research and Scholarly Works is a peer-reviewed, fully-indexed journal that showcases scholarly work from undergraduates in all fields.The journal publishes long abstracts, posters, papers, reviews, and submissions of unique formats of visual/auditory material.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Near &amp; Middle-Eastern Civilizations</title>
      <URL>https://jps.library.utoronto.ca/index.php/nmcjournal</URL>
      <institution>University of Toronto</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Near &amp; Middle-Eastern Civilizations is a yearly journal published by the University of Toronto NMC Students' Union. It seeks to receive work from both graduate and undergraduate students--particularly in relation to the modern Middle East.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Virginia Journal of Gender Studies</title>
      <URL>https://www.vjgs.org/</URL>
      <institution>University of Virginia</institution>
      <description>The Virginia Journal of Gender Studies is the only undergraduate research publication in the United States dedicated to feminist and queer scholarship. The journal was founded to provide opportunities for undergraduate students to contribute their research to the field of women, gender, and sexuality studies, as well as to increase access to academic publishing.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Intersections</title>
      <URL>http://depts.washington.edu/chid/intersections_Spring_2012/index.html</URL>
      <institution>University of Washington</institution>
      <description>Intersections is an interdisciplinary print-form journal published online by the Comparative History of Ideas program at the University of Washington, Seattle. Intersections features features student essays, research papers, and capstone theses in the Arts, Humanities, and Social Sciences. There are no established deadlines as submissions are accepted on a rolling basis. Work of any length is considered. Interested authors should consult the journal's Call for Papers page for submission specifications. Authors can contact the editorial staff at: intersectionssubmissions@gmail.com.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Process: Journal of Multidisciplinary Undergraduate Scholarship</title>
      <URL>https://www.processjmus.org/</URL>
      <institution>University of Washington</institution>
      <description>Process: Journal of Multidisciplinary Undergraduate Scholarship provides a space for undergraduate writers to share their work outside of the context and constraints of the college classroom. Each issue of Process centers on a topic of contemporary interest to a global audience, fostering critical conversations that transverse disciplinary, cultural, and national borders. We believe that undergraduate writing deserves serious attention, and hope to encourage writers to begin forging new pathways for the future of academic and public scholarship.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Jackson School Journal of International Studies</title>
      <URL>https://jsis.washington.edu/jsjournal/</URL>
      <institution>University of Washington </institution>
      <description>The Jackson School Journal is an online and print publication dedicated to profiling the outstanding research and policy writing relating to international studies.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>LURe</title>
      <URL>https://www.westga.edu/lure/</URL>
      <institution>University of West Georgia</institution>
      <description>LURe (Literary Undergraduate Research in English) publishes undergraduate scholarship in literature, critical theory, film, and cultural studies. The journal invites submissions from across the country, and publishes select peer-reviewed submissions once a year in both a digital and a print copy.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Oshkosh Scholar</title>
      <URL>https://www.uwosh.edu/osscap/present/oshkosh-scholar</URL>
      <institution>University of Wisconsin Oshkosh</institution>
      <description>Oshkosh Scholar is a faculty-reviewed undergraduate research journal published annually by University of Wisconsin Oshkosh's Office of Student Research and Creativity.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Kinesiology Research</title>
      <URL>http://minds.wisconsin.edu/handle/1793/23588</URL>
      <institution>University of Wisconsin- Eau Claire</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Undergraduate Kinesiology Research is published by the Kinesiology Department at the University of Wisconsin - Eau Claire. The peer reviewed, Internet-based journal (ISSN 1936-7007) is dedicated to original undergraduate research in Kinesiology. The Editor-In-Chief invites Kinesiology-related, undergraduate research from all academic institutions.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Madison Journal of Literary Criticism</title>
      <URL>http://english.wisc.edu/TheMJLC/</URL>
      <institution>University of Wisconsin-Madison</institution>
      <description>The Madison Journal of Literary Criticism aims to provide a forum for undergraduate students to publish their scholarly work and engage in the contemporary literary debates ongoing in the larger academic community.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Interpersonal Relations, Intergroup Relations and Identity</title>
      <URL>http://jiriri.ca/</URL>
      <institution>Université de Montréal</institution>
      <description>Title of Journal: Journal of Interpersonal Relations, Intergroup Relations and Identity (JIRIRI). Years active: 2008 – present Peer-reviewed: yes Review done by: undergraduate and graduate students. A senior associate editor (Ph.D.) trains the students and verifies all the letters that are sent to the authors. The Journal of Interpersonal Relations, Intergroup Relations and Identity (JIRIRI) is a social psychology journal with the goal of promoting the creation and expression of novel theoretical and empirical ideas. Created at Université de Montréal, it is an international scientific peer-reviewed journal for undergraduate students. The JIRIRI’s goal is to promote creative and original ideas in social psychology and related fields, produced by undergraduate students worldwide. Undergraduate students are given the opportunity to either publish an empirical or theoretical manuscript, to review scientific manuscripts or to become part of the editorial team. The JIRIRI’s next goal is to diffuse its material to other professors and students that wish to use the peer-review process as a teaching tool.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>DISCOVER: Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://digitalcommons.usu.edu/urj/</URL>
      <institution>Utah State University</institution>
      <description>DISCOVER is a peer-reviewed, open access journal dedicated to the publication of outstanding scholarship by undergraduates at Utah State University. This journal accepts submissions of scholarly and research articles, from undergraduate students in all academic disciplines.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Vanderbilt Historical Review</title>
      <URL>http://vanderbilthistoricalreview.com/</URL>
      <institution>Vanderbilt University</institution>
      <description>The Vanderbilt Historical Review (VHR) is the first and only journal of history at Vanderbilt. The publication seeks to show the importance of studying the past through its semiannual publication of historical research. Topics may cover a wide range of disciplines, including economics, politics, anthropology, and more. The editorial board leads a blind review process in which historically accurate, interesting, and creative articles are critiqued. Undergraduate students at any university are encouraged to submit their work. The journal provides a forum of academic debate over relevant historical questions.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Vanderbilt Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>http://ejournals.library.vanderbilt.edu/ojs/index.php/vurj/index</URL>
      <institution>Vanderbilt University</institution>
      <description>The Vanderbilt Undergraduate Research Journal (VURJ) is a joint venture between faculty and students that is sponsored by the Office of the Provost. It is the university's premier venue for multidisciplinary student research.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Vassar College Journal of Philosophy</title>
      <URL>http://philosophy.vassar.edu/students/journal/</URL>
      <institution>Vassar College </institution>
      <description>The Vassar College Journal of Philosophy is a student-run publication supported by the Philosophy Department of Vassar College. Dedicated to both quality and accessibility, it seeks to give undergraduate students from all disciplines a platform to express and discuss philosophical ideas. The Journal is published once a year, in the spring, both in print and online.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Auctus</title>
      <URL>http://www.auctus.vcu.edu</URL>
      <institution>Virginia Commonwealth University</institution>
      <description>Auctus: The Journal of Undergraduate Research and Creative Scholarship is designed to highlight the various forms of research taking place at Virginia Commonwealth University. The journal is student-run, peer-reviewed, and edited with assistance from faculty members. Auctus accepts outstanding submissions from VCU undergraduates of all disciplines. The journal welcomes submissions of research articles, technical papers, expository articles, and works of creative scholarship.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Journal of Undergraduate Chemistry Research</title>
      <URL>http://www.vmi.edu/content.aspx?id=2150</URL>
      <institution>Virginia Military Institute</institution>
      <description>The Journal of Undergraduate Chemistry Research is a new peer review journal that will be published quarterly with papers of original research performed by undergraduates on all aspects of chemistry, including analytical, organic, inorganic, physical, polymers and biochemistry. Authorship may be by the student or their professor.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Philologia: Undergraduate Research Journal for Liberal Arts and Human Sciences</title>
      <URL>https://philologiavt.org/</URL>
      <institution>Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State
                                                University </institution>
      <description>Philologia is Greek for "scholarship, love of learning," a title that embodies the objectives of the journal. The journal was created for the College of Liberal Arts and Human Sciences at Virginia Tech and accepts liberal arts research from all 13 Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC) universities.It is an annually published, multidisciplinary peer-reviewed journal.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Philosophy, Politics, and Economics Review: An International Undergraduate Journal</title>
      <URL>https://pressbooks.lib.vt.edu/pper/</URL>
      <institution>Virginia Tech</institution>
      <description>The Philosophy, Politics, and Economics Review is an international undergraduate journal housed in the Kellogg Center for Philosophy, Politics, and Economics at Virginia Tech. The journal is dedicated to publishing original research in philosophy, politics, and economics and the humanities and social sciences more generally. The journal welcomes submissions from current or recent undergraduate students in PPE and related fields worldwide.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>ERIS VU Journal for Humanities</title>
      <URL>https://erisjournal.com/</URL>
      <institution>Vrije Universiteit (VU) Amsterdam</institution>
      <description>ERIS aims to publish articles of humanities students of all universities. ERIS publishes regular issues and essay prizes bi-annually.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Righting Wrongs: A Journal of Human Rights</title>
      <URL>http://blogs.webster.edu/humanrights/</URL>
      <institution>Webster University</institution>
      <description>Righting Wrongs: A Journal of Human Rights is a peer-reviewed academic journal that provides space for students to explore human rights issues, challenge current actions and frameworks, and engage in problem-solving aimed at tackling some of the world’s most pressing issues.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Glocality</title>
      <URL>https://www.glocality.eu/</URL>
      <institution>Windesheim Honours College, The
                                                Netherlands</institution>
      <description>Glocality is an open-access academic journal that offers a platform to undergraduate students to share their work with the scholar community and practitioners worldwide. Articles explore the relationship between local and global on the dimensions of the Sustainable Development Goals.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>WPI Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://wurj.org/</URL>
      <institution>Worcester Polytechnic Institute</institution>
      <description>The WPI Undergraduate Research Journal (WURJ) provides a venue to share impressive research achievements with the campus and larger academic community. Published annually in the spring semester, WURJ features high-quality articles written by undergraduate students presenting findings from interactive qualifying projects (IQPs), major qualifying projects (MQPs), independent study projects, and class projects. WURJ is completely organized by a panel of graduate student volunteers that reviews and selects submissions based on rigorous criteria, and the review process is competitive.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>XULAneXUS</title>
      <URL>http://xulanexus.xula.edu/textpattern/</URL>
      <institution>Xavier University of Louisiana</institution>
      <description>XULAneXUS is a refereed online journal that publishes the scholarship of Xavier University of Louisiana undergraduates. First published in 2002, the journal is sponsored by the Center for Undergraduate Research and Graduate Opportunity and originally funded in part by the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation. XULAneXUS publishes undergraduate research in every academic discipline at Xavier through annual or bi-annual online volumes. The journal is divided into four sections: Research Manuscripts, Creative Scholarship, Scholarly Notes, and Service-Learning Analyses. Submissions are reviewed by an interdisciplinary editorial board consisting of faculty and students. The journal supports a wide range of submissions, including traditional research manuscripts, scholarly essays, visual and audio representations of creative scholarship, and multimedia components embedded within manuscripts.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Yale Historical Review</title>
      <URL>https://www.yalehistoricalreview.org</URL>
      <institution>Yale University</institution>
      <description>The Yale Historical Review provides undergraduates an opportunity to have their exceptional work highlighted and encourages the diffusion of original historical ideas on college campuses by providing a forum for outstanding undergraduate papers covering any historical topic.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>Yale Undergraduate Research Journal</title>
      <URL>https://yurj.yale.edu/</URL>
      <institution>Yale University</institution>
      <description>The Yale Undergraduate Research Journal was established in spring 2020 and is the first reviewed publication to span the disciplinary breadth of research conducted by Yale students. Twice a year, YURJ publishes recent work from the humanities, social sciences, and STEM fields online and in print.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Politic</title>
      <URL>http://thepolitic.org/</URL>
      <institution>Yale University </institution>
      <description>The Politic is a quarterly magazine that strives to inform the greater Yale community about the most important local, national, and global political happenings.</description>
   </journal>
   <journal>
      <title>The Yale Review of Undergraduate Research in Psychology</title>
      <URL>http://www.yale.edu/yrurp/</URL>
      <institution>Yale University </institution>
      <description>The Yale Review of Undergraduate Research in Psychology is an annual journal that showcases the best and most original research in psychology conducted by undergraduates from around the world. They publish research in all areas of psychology, including clinical, developmental, cognitive, and social psychology. Their goal is to contribute to the scientific advance by encouraging serious, quality research early in students' academic careers. We provide a platform for undergraduate scientists to share their findings, and aim to bring together a community of young psychologists from both the United States and abroad.</description>
   </journal>
</journals_list>
